cards laid out for show star shine is so bright watch the secrets unfold there's magic in her
hands whisper what the future holds
door feel the romance in every arcane war
Those there was five people here. So the three people that left during that song
Let me say
Oh lurkers they're lurkers
Lur
I don't know what happened guys
What it just takes your best friend telling you to unalive yourself a few times to like
Well, not my best friend probably the worst enemy
You're being gang I heard some pot I'm probably to smoke that and fall asleep forget all about this
Did she didn't did she deny it
Is she hiding?
Come to your conclusion
You go watch Little Nightmares say man's playing Little Nightmares go watch him go watch him play Little Nightmares
Leave the real nightmare and go see Sam and playing Little Nightmares
You don't want to see this. This is this is like a car crash
It'd be difficult to look away, but too brutal to stomach
Okay
Okay, well no one wants to talk to me,
except for Pierce being good.
So I'll probably just go away.
But, thanks anyway guys.
that is. Did anyone deny it? No. Even a denial would be given. I mean, I will. Okay. But
even in a denial would be nicer than a, it's called a confession. What's wrong? Everything.
Sorry, nothing's all right
Infiltrate destroy build who's infiltrating what you you nick
Okay, you can infiltrate a snail
And he's slow
It's okay, I'm just kidding this go ahead infiltrate me
Destroy good luck
I only had a beer. I still have time to get another one if I want.
What time is it? 9.45? Maybe five minutes?
I can still get in the store. I still have half this left to go.
Snail. Yeah. Go infiltrate a snail.
I'm gonna snail stash it in me probably. All right.
What's wrong? Look at my community wall. You can find out what's wrong.
Find out what's wrong
Used to
We used to have a place called Moonstone Beach here and
These beautiful Moonstones would come washing the shore every year they wash up every year
There's little beats these Moonstones will wash up and Moonstones are valuable
They decided to like dig it all up to like use for the power plant
Foundation and so there's no moonstone beach anymore
Why do we destroy what's like most beautiful in the world? I don't understand
Why the humans do that wind is what supposedly happened Ray
Moonstone Beach happened before it happened when Redondo Beach was called Moonstone Beach before they destroyed Moonstone Beach
Then it became redondo
Look it up
When did what supposedly happen?
Tell me tell me ray
You rave sunshine
Ray ray ray ray ray
Tell me you tell me
Oh, okay, well be no beta said that about a month ago
She said oh sake he said he was gonna unalive himself. She's like just do it. Don't tell me just do it do it bitch
She said something like that
You never heard boy do you watch the beat of 24 hours a day Ray you wouldn't have heard it it wasn't clipped or anything
But I heard it. I heard it. I found it. She's syndicated on rumble and I heard it
When she said she said it this morning again never contact me again. It might as well be dead, right?
It doesn't Ray. Well, maybe she just wouldn't do it to you
But but I lie when I lie about it
She actually had like a few people on the panel and they all were saying it
They all were saying it. It's a it's the Aaron Carter
Syndrome. Oh
This person's weird
They're different. They're on drugs. They're just weird. You don't like him for some reason
Let's destroy him
No, it didn't it took me a month because it happened again this morning. I
Need like I need a double to confirm things. I need to happen this many times like that
that many
She count to I
Talked about it before too. I talked about it before I told it when it happened, but I
Need to happen twice and it did
sweet
sweet confirmation
Did she deny it?
She told me this morning
I'll read the message
I'll tell you what I wrote and what she wrote back
Okay, you can judge you're trying to understand this. Okay, good
Beta I
Said okay a few days ago. I just okay few days ago
No one loves me for real when I disappear sorry keep making fun of me call me names. I don't care anymore
Here's what she said. I just woke up to feed the kiddies. I don't make fun of you
I care about you more than you think please don't say stuff like that. I'm hurting too cry face cry face
Love you. Please eat and get rest
Then me today
Pie my black cat one of my black cats came home the other day for a little while he rubbed my leg before he left
I miss you. Hope you're good. Thanks for coming to my chat today. Hope we can work everything out sometime and still be friends
Love you. Take care. Here's what she replied and then I put this little motion. You can't see it
It's just a little rabid with like setting love from his heart, right?
And then she said, I was not in your chat today, nor have for a long time, stop lying
on my name.
You messaged me at 3 AM Saturday, tell me you miss me and hit your life.
Did you tell your audience that?
Nope, you are too scared.
Do not contact me anymore and enjoy the evil around you, take care.
And I said, oh, it was a fake you.
I can't really tell the difference and neither can anyone else.
Alex was right around you.
You know, it's just so she didn't say it there, but it might as well have
That remember that triggered the
She did well, she did on her other show. It was another show
I have to can I go through thousands of hours on rumble where she said do it. Just do it the nike
You know, what is she the spokesperson for nike? Just do it
Might as well well because i'm dead to her right never contact me again
After I said oh
You know, I miss you or something or I hope you're well
What'd I say? I
Said miss you. Hope you're good. Thanks for coming to my chat today
Hope we can work everything out sometime and still be friends. Love you. Take care reply
I was not in your chat today nor have I been for a long time. Stop lying on my name. You messaged me Saturday at 3
I'm telling you you miss me and hate your life. Did you tell your audience that nope? You are too scared
You're not contacting me anymore and enjoy the evil around you. Take care
All right, so that's I just repeated it again
Is that that's the appropriate response to like I miss you is it?
Ray I told you fucking three times she said it last month. I don't have the clip
I will go to rumble and find the fucking clip
Dumbass, who are you ray? Who are you? Who are your real identity ray? Who are you? I know you
I know I know I recognize the energy to tell me who you are though
You just didn't appear here not a mod not a not a member you disappeared ray
Exiled one it's exiled one. Okay. I know who you are Bronzeberg sister-in-law. I
Want to talk I'm talking right now
Kestoff. Oh, you think I'm kestostriphizing things. BG. BG is a faggot
And I'm more honest than that
Bitch
Bitchy goon is what BG stands for
Big giraffe
Bitch ass goofy, but that'd be bad. I know you are right you're exiled one or his brother-in-law
Bronzeberg, I like the sister-in-law person. She's cool. Oh
You're opening a cat sanctuary. Well, Jamie. I'm sorry, Jamie gets my cats panda face
You can, I hope you get anally penetrated
while being tied down in a panda costume, okay?
That's my wish for you.
If I had one wish right now, that would be my wish.
Jamie gets the cats, so no, I'm not sending to a sanctuary.
I'm looking for Morris Day.
Morris Day, Bronze Bird, Bronze Bird, Bronze Bird.
Okay, that's Bronze Bird and Ray is exiled one.
I called it, I'm so smart.
How do I so smart?
Panda face. Yep. Look, panda face. I love you, panda face.
You know what Jim Nick loves? Jim Nick loves fishing for sympathy with
fake cancer. That's what Jim Nick loves.
You say I'm fishing for sympathy. Do I say I have cancer?
I asked for $10 for for fish tacos. No, actually, for dad.
Did I ask for $10 so I could have a car to take me to the hospital?
So I could go get a bottle of alcohol?
Sorry, my father passed away from cancer last year, so people that do that kind of shit, that pisses me off.
Okay, Morris Day. Did I mention Morris Day? Who's Morris Day? You're probably Bita.
Minnetonka? How about Morris Day? How about you fuck yourself?
Ray she was seen after she asked for $10 so she could get a car to the hospital
She was seen by a bottle of like Jack Daniels at the liquor store
You can just come to your own judgment
She also said it went into read she also said it was um, what is it?
Benign she said but malignant
Okay, so Malignant means it's taking over benign mean it was nothing. She said it was benign
It doesn't turn cancer
Tumor is turned from Malignant to benign not cancer
Mmm, just what I know I
Have a dick shut up Ray. You're so stupid
Jamie can you hide him or time out for like an hour or something?
I don't feel like seeing his dumb comments. It's like too dumb for me right now
It sounds drunk. Well, I had just one and a half hard lemonade. Is that like so drunk?
Hey, go. Hey, Sandman is playing little months little nightmares
Yeah, J dogs my boyfriend. Yeah. Yeah, Puder. So what? I'm gonna fuck with J dog
Okay, $10 cash up panda face and I'll read your cards
Cash up psyche awakens or else I don't trust you until unless you was on her live you can relate to your end-stage cirrhosis
If I had end-stage cirrhosis, I wouldn't be fucking around in this community on YouTube
But this would be the last place I would be if I end-stage cirrhosis I would be laying in a bed passing away
Okay, Panda. Well, sorry, I don't have a car for you, Jim Nick, whoever you are.
What is me?
That's me, what? Oh, that's me?
Well, the point is, if you're an end stage cirrhosis, you couldn't do anything besides lying in a bed thing that is.
If you had stage four cirrhosis, you would be walking around.
Going to chance channels they don't the pictures of me my diaper. I don't have anything against Jim neck really it's just whatever
Beliefer
Right. Oh, it takes years. Okay stage four and stage cirrhosis and say you know what end stage means and say does not mean years
The end means the end
Okay, I
Understand the end stage, okay
It means and means
At the longest a year the longest and that year you're not gonna be spooking around on YouTube
Little battery knows little battery knows
Cuz the thought you don't want superheroes Jamie pooter to hide pooter
hide
Panda face
That's good and hi Ray or you can just time him up for 24 hours. I
Don't want to go here or anything. So is that smoking tobacco nicotine?
Waiting for weed to get here. Oh
Good horn, they just call me back home, but Zilla here we go home
11 p.m. E.T.A. one one hour
Guys keep me awake until 11
You know what a panda is pandas aren't even a real animal
There's some unfortunate guy in a panda costume, which is just a fake thing, you know
Pandas can't even reproduce according. I
Looks like I was born out of a big bitch. I think I think Nick Johnson is a big vagina. That's my opinion on Nick
Nick Johnson
My opinion on Nick Johnson
I'm gonna tell Tony on you okay, so Puder is Tony. Hey, by the way, go check out Tony's mom on Onlyfans
I think she has an eight dollar um eight dollar sign up fee for um for ally master computers mom
She's not only fans. Hmm. Since you decided not take my deal
My deal was like shut the fuck up and stop sending things to my house Tony
I'm gonna tell about your mom on Onlyfans for eight dollars. Okay, and we have your dad's number two
I can't reproduce because I'm gay.
Some of that made my semen doesn't work anymore.
That means that anybody that is artificially inseminated
to get pregnant, right?
Now now unban him. Oh my gosh. I'm at fifth stage racist. Oh my god. It was Tony
Tony you're mad. Come on
Sorry Tony
Sorry Tony Tony Tony
Racist racist. Hey chicken cakes. I
Have a link. It's just for chicken cakes though. She wants to come up. I like her
Shut up, Tony! Stop texting me! Tony, stop texting me! Tony, stop texting me, motherfucker!
This is all text from Tony. Do you hear that sound? These are all Tony's texts right now.
There we go. Uh-oh. Your name is copyrighted. Let's see it. Let's see it, bitch. Let's see it.
Oh, you said my name, John. Wow. Wow. Wow.
Hmm. Yeah, who's saying my name? What the hell? What is he saying? I don't want to read it.
BG. BG is the biggest bitch. I saw BG in a gay porno movie being gang banged by ten black guys, okay?
And to contact me personally, I will show you this porno. Okay?
Yeah, Grease Pit. This is where the gooner session is.
Oh, go dig up John senior and tell him. Okay, so go dig up my father. You don't want to dig up my father because he will fucking kill you
Okay
Go look up. Oh lying on BG now. Oh, so BG and an alley master if you have something going. Okay. Anyway, yeah
I'm a greasy bastard. Okay
Chicken cakes you come on, please. I just want to talk to chicken cakes though. Nobody else
Nobody else take except for chicken cakes, and I will verify it's her
My father's name is my name. It's the same it's the same thing. I
Am my father. There's no difference. I am my father's vengeance
That's why I was born
Tell the police that the meth I smoke, okay? I'll tell them about the dildos you had up your ass
How about that?
Chicken cakes you're chosen. You're the chosen one chicken cakes chosen CCC 333. It just makes sense to me. Oh
Never be called a diddler. This is by Allied Master Computer
To calling me a diddler, okay?
Allied Master Computer. I have your fucking receipts. Oh my god
I'm not mad at you Paige. I just said you you know you could have like said, you know be that don't tell people to kill themselves
It's okay. You don't have to
I'm blaming you because you're Jewish. I'm fucking Ashkenazi. What are you talking about? Yes, you are Tony. I know. I know you are
I didn't delete my last stream you're sending scrappers. Oh, what else is new?
The scrappers are all mad at you. You're gonna have a scrapper. I am Jewish. I'm Ashkenazi. Okay, bitch. Oh
I'm getting a mad now
Now I'm cooked now, I'm cooked
Well, I probably your Thanksgiving dinner 1989 bitch pretending to be Jewish is a hate crime
Okay
Do you want blood tests? Oh?
Oh
ADL anti. It's AD
Hold on ADL anti-deformation League
Justine, thank you. Oh, I'm gonna make sure it's a real justine. I love justine
Oh, hey, hey, I just wanted to really quickly tell you that I think your music ability is fucking amazing. I like your dark shit.
It's really good. I'm a techno crazy, crazy chick and I love all that techno stuff since like 1993 or maybe even 1990.
I love techno with a, you have no idea, like the chemical brothers, Scooter, you know, like fucking Rez, dead mouths.
Rez? I like Rez too.
Rez and what's there? There's a Rez song called she's with she was another chick. Hold on. She's it's really cool
I can't play any more
Copyright music back and tell you her name. No Rezes. You know Rez is Canadian
Yes, I love Canadian people. Yeah, and you know what dead mouse dead mouse
And Rez is Canadian
But there's a we are not only that
Marsh Marshmallow man, I think is Canadian and we have a lot of amazing
That's happening. Yes. I am I am
From I'm from I'm from Abbotsford, BC
Okay, British Columbia. Okay. That's that's in the west side
Okay, like Vancouver by Vancouver area
I have an assignment for you, Justine, um, because this is a read.
The assignment is watched, um, a video by, her name is Dove Cameron, D-O-V-E-C-A-M-E-R-O-N,
with R-E-Z-Z, with Rez, it's called Taste of You.
I like that.
Oh my God, Taste of You, I love that!
I fucking you know why I love I love poet um puzzle box I love the first one I love it was um
it is the silliest video but it's the best it's uh come on a man man is and now I'm being stupid
man is
Yeah, and now I love menace.
That was the very first song in the bit of music I listened to.
And it's a stupid snake video, but the music is to die for.
There's no, there's no words to it.
It's just pure music.
Well, you're awesome.
Like, have you been lately?
Did you, are you able to talk to my chat?
Yeah, you are.
Cause that's how you're crawling in my chat.
So you're not blocked in my chat.
And okay, good.
So that's good.
No, I'm not gonna block your chat you were blocking my chat. Do you like JT, right?
Yes, I love JT. Okay, cuz JT is here. Hold on
Do you want to know what's cool about AJT?
I love my JT.
JT's in the house.
Uh-oh, it's JT.
Ah, JT.
Justine, what are you what are you been doing justine? I have been dating I have been going to school
I have been living a fan fucking tastic life
That's that's what I want to hear
You know that cake I made I'm still going out with that guy that I made the cake for
How many years how many years ago was that I don't know
That's great. Hey, tell these nice people about how what I do all the nice things I did
Can I tell you something that JT did to me for me for real?
No fucking lie. He gave me some really good advice as how to handle my dad
because my dad
Was I have a learning disability? I'm dyslexic and I have ADHD blah blah blah and he was never there
He never invested in me and make a very long story short
I felt very ugly and very disgusted
and very discarded from my father.
And then JT told me to tell my dad
to have the balls enough to tell my dad what you feel
and all those good things.
And I did what he said.
And now me and my father are besties.
Do you know that?
Do you know that psyche that me and my dad are besties because of JT?
That's good.
Well, I didn't block this person.
He's saying, are you saying Justine is using a DMCA copyright image?
Well, I think that's her own image, so...
No, that's me!
Yeah. That's me. Somebody said that that's that's fake. It's AMC whose mom's on on uh
Only fans for eight dollars. Yeah
Well, this is that's my picture. That is the real what I look like. Oh, they think you're
I'm sorry. I'm stunning. I'm sorry. I'm stunning, but that's me
Yeah, they think you're trying to catfish. I'm trying to pull one over on us. Justina
Yeah, yeah, yeah
We didn't do that
And uh, yeah, I'm gonna put my glasses on so
Quit I'm sorry. No, I'm just like saying don't you think his music mean JT?
Don't you think psyche's music is amazing? No, I heard some of that like it was like some gothic music or something
That was a mind that was like I was playing at the end. I was playing as been called skinned. That was pretty cool
But I
Tagged you in the the CFF song chat friends forever song. I saw that I like that. I'm a fan of that. I like that
Yeah
And, but I, yeah, go ahead, I'm sorry.
Chat friends are forever, forever, I'm not forever, I'm not a CFF-er, I'm not a CFF-er.
Well, you're also gonna be, you will be in your heart, you know, forever.
Yeah.
I, you know who I am, I, I, I call it CFFers, but my CFFer is JT, Rain, Gaudi, and Ms, Ms, I call her Les Mis, but Ms. Liz.
Oh, she's great. She's a mod too here. Ms. Liz is a mod.
She is the best lady in the whole world. She is like she...
She has helped me too. She's like a JT, a female form of a JT, and she's also got amazing education too.
So she's a teacher, I think. I don't know what she does, but she's always been very nice to me.
And right no, I think oh, yeah, I shouldn't say stuff like that. I don't know nothing
Justine justine. I am don't listen. No one should ever listen to me. I don't know anything. You know, no
Me no, I know nothing either. I
Pick at the English
Yeah, I
Thought I I pick at the berries so I can buy my condominium
So, Fikey, what's, do I even want to ask
what's going on with you and Vita?
I know nothing, I don't even know if I want to know
what's going on.
Well, Vita told me that I'm alive myself.
Really, that's kind of shocking.
Why would she say that?
Yeah, well, ask Aaron Carter.
That's fucked up.
You know, I could understand you guys
have a little fight or something,
but I think that's pretty fucked up for a friend to say that.
If you've heard the message what I said, I said, I said.
Hey, I love you. I miss you and then no responses like off yourself because I fucking miss her. That's horrible
What the fuck? Yeah, wow
Wow, you think you know a person
Maybe not. I don't know. I don't know. You never know who anybody I'm supposed to be doing homework
And I don't want to do my homework because I do want to do my homework and I'm very excited about what I'm taking
But I'm kind of a procrastinator. Oh
Yeah, you're
Fascinating. What do you study? Do you want if I ask what are you studying? No, I'm not telling anybody. Oh, that's okay
No, you know what? I mean, it's better without because I don't know how what these walls are secure. So
No, no, no, it's okay. I'll tell you I'll tell you in secret one day, but not now
I trust you because what the hell what why would you what were you back like like?
I think it's I think people say too much on these places
I'm not gonna be very much longer and so this is the record. This is just like people know what happened
That's why I'm saying okay. I don't expect anything. I mean not not you guys, but I'm saying that's what I'm saying
I said I say things because people are out here in the chat. Well, I didn't know I don't know
What's going on?
Who is that in the picture?
That is, that's my brother.
Your brother.
He's Kamala Harris.
Yeah, but you didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, my big brother right there.
Yeah.
All right
Rain do you want the link tell me rain yourself? It's rain has eraser. Rain has to say the modern race or not somebody else
Eraser rain
Eraser rain is erasing rain is one of the most
Mm-hmm. Go ahead. I'm sorry. I'm gonna say one of the most delightful women. I really I don't really like women very much
I don't like women at all
But I like rain. She's got very good kind heart
Which most women don't have I agree. She's like
Porcupine she's like if you're like
Kind of appear. Oh, yeah, she
If she if she has to defend people she is like a pitfall
Yeah, she can be pretty ruthless when she needs to be but she's very
Confirm that I am the the high priest of a see at that
For what we needed a high priest, so he did fill out the job application now
We're still we're still screening, but I'm pretty sure you got the spot. Thank you. Well, you can have my you can have my
My my slot I give my my my membership to you psyche
So now you're in the club because I've given you my dues. I given them my dues for you
Well, I think for you Christine, I think you are like one of those unofficial CFF or you're like under the you're like under the table
Okay, the very first time my mom had cider when I was a little tiny girl, it tasted like pop to me. So I drank the whole bottle and my mom found me passed out under the table.
I was eight. I did not know what alcohol was. I was eight.
I just thought I was eight. Like, like, um, like, like pop, like, cool. Like, like, like, what is
the apple pop? I had no idea that it was alcohol in it. Was it good? Did you get drunk? It was
fucking good. Well, I'm worried, I'm worried that I pinned a page page. I don't blame you for anything
I know you're your own people. I don't blame you. Oh, I've had the link up for for rain. I'm sorry. I didn't I didn't press enter
Um, I think page like came in and she said, whoa, do you still blame me and I don't I don't I don't blame page
But for what no blame for what?
For telling me that I'm alive myself. Oh, well, she didn't do it. It was the other one that did it. Yeah
I know so I'm just telling you I don't blame her
Really left cuz I don't blame you know what people tell me to go in and well not really
I haven't really been I've been told to go and do that, but I've had people tell me to go fuck myself
To go and fuck myself
Yeah, and tell you're on a left. Yeah, like do it to do it until you're
So you're no longer with it.
Yeah, go fuck yourself.
Go fuck yourself to death.
There you go.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
You know what I used to have a dog. I used to wear it when I used to clean and I had my own company and stuff
I have this dog. His name was midnight and he was a Doverman pincher
him and me were the best of buddies. I love that dog and he loved me and he was
just a lowly dog in a like a like a worker dog and me and him because of me
he became part of the family and I really fucking love that dog. He miss
Me either time I look at the dog in the face a little bit, huh?
You know like one of those poodle the black poodles kind of yeah kind of like you know what I'm saying
I wasn't the only one to think that
Doverman pinchers. I went right I guess it right away, right? No. Yeah, right away
And then this guy, he looks like God, what would I compare it to?
E?
Hold on, are you talking to me?
No.
I'm talking about this.
Oh, midnight.
Oh, so that's Sam, man.
He looks like, yeah, in front of things, too.
It's giving Krusty the clown.
I don't know what that's.
Yeah.
Krusty the clown.
Krusty the clown, you're not lying.
When he takes off his makeup.
He looks like Frosty the clown without the makeup
Yeah, I mean he looks like some Simpsons character if he's not a Simpson. He's definitely a simp. I'm a Simpsons
I'm a I'm a Simpson phallic. I have socks. I have little figurines. I had like some
DVDs I love the Simpsons. Oh, are you like a huge Simpsons fan? I'm gonna give
Yes, but I'm more of a family guy. I'm more family guy than the Simpsons
Oh, the things that make you happy.
You know, I do still like it and then like I don't know it kind of fell off
Maybe maybe it's just me, but I feel like family guy kind of was good. The first yeah in the middle
In the middle it did. Yeah, like in the beginning like the first two maybe three. I don't know before
Is rain is Aztec warrior, right? Yeah
Okay, one second
Rain
They say it never rains in California rain. Is that you what up?
Yeah, hey rain. Hey rain. Hey, justine. I love you. Hey, psyche
Come in now. You're still here 10 minutes later if you said you're gonna leave already
See they love you so much. Hi psyche. Hi rain. How are you sweetheart? Good. How are you?
I'm good. I have wheat coming in 40 minutes. I have to stay awake until then
I want to know did you bleach your hair because it looks like
I got these rubber bands, I got these rubber bands, and so I don't think I should go back to it.
I don't think I should go back to it.
Oh, Justin, feel free to mute yourself, Justin, at any time.
You guys heard me cough like that?
Just get closer to the phone and go...
I love you. I'm sorry. I thought I turned it off
You can't can I tell you what I'm smoking psyche
I'm smoking 90
97%
Indica vape weed
It's not for good little girls. Are you waiting for delivery or what? Yeah, it's coming at 11 p.m. Yeah
So you didn't bleach your hair. No, but I used to get highlights, but no, it's just the light on top of it
But yeah, it's yeah, it looks lighter to me. I was born with like the color of my wig
This is my hair when I was born
Me too
Why me too? I have white blonde hair when I was born
Swear to God
Hair and blue eyes and blue wide
I don't know. I don't know.
What happened?
I don't know.
My care changed colors. I don't
know.
I used to get mad at my mother
and I used to say she washed
out my blonde.
Bitch!
Hey, Gotti, get the hell up here.
Justine wants to sing the Gotti song.
Justine, can you start the Gotti song until he comes up?
The Gotti song.
Okay, just one second. I'm going to mic it. Get the music ready. Yes. We want to hear it. She's getting her guitar ready
Justine is like a master musician. I love it
Yes
He's the overseer
Let's all sing it
Everywhere he goes everywhere he goes
I want to follow him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him, him
So like you get your gun out
Did you like that that's how you know it's time for mass
Yeah, do you want to know did you like that that was that was that was interpretive guitar?
Nice, Justine.
Hi, Mr. Taiki, Mr. Taiki.
Mr. Taiki, hello.
I'm a really nice little girl. I'm such a nice little girl. I just like Hitler
I come to warn you about that the CFF the NPD and the flying monkeys
The J turds I come to warn you about the CFF the flying monkey crew, you know range. She's a fake
Yeah, the J turds the NPD
You know what she paints her face and she's like a fucking follower of me and she hates me she tells me she hates me and then she paints her face exact not exactly because she's a terrible pain face painter, but she paints her face and she makes fun of the original.
Look justine justine justine did it first, okay, so there there will be no cheap imitations justine
Can you yeah, I think it's like she's copying me and she has the audacity to say that I'm old and passé
But she's following an old passé girl. That's 54
Do you have or do you have the paint?
No, I'm not doing that anymore because people make fun of me too much. Oh darn. Well, those people can go far far go
Yeah
Well Slayer has more wrinkles than you do justine
Yeah, I mean honestly like I'm 50 fucking four and I don't really have wrinkles. I don't really have any gray hair
And I'm completely and I have a very spry body like I climb up things and I jump off the bridges and I go down very steep
zip lines
I'm very old, but I can fucking do anything a fucking 34 year old can do even better
I'm gonna jump off a zip line
You don't want to do that silly boy
Oh silly boy, I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do a backflip off the cliff
No, don't do it, because you know what?
If you go and fall off a zip truck line, you're dead.
You have nothing to help you.
You have no lines, nothing.
All you have to do is take a cat, you like put a piece of bread on the cat with the butter
side up, and then you strap the cat to yourself, and then if you jump the cat will land on
its feet, you'll survive.
Exactly.
That's perfectly right.
Pull the butter side up, paradigm.
And Joni, come on, hang out with us. We're having a little...
Well, I went crazy, but everyone else is pretty sane, relatively, to me, at least.
Well, I'm not... I'm being very good and on my best behavior, but I'm not very sane.
I want you to act up.
Hey, Gotti's here! Gotti's here!
Everywhere he goes, I want to follow him.
God, he has a nice body.
See, that's not normal.
That was beautiful.
Thank you
That was so beautiful
Touch it summoned me. That was great. I
Thank you. I was calling the gods. I have see I have such a beautiful siren voice
That I call the gods
No, I know I've got I've got a very like
Sorry, I'm sorry. I'm just kidding. No, I know. No, no, no, cuz a little marina is a siren. That's a bad joke. I'm sorry. That was terrible.
I like, I like, um...
I'm like you're a picture gaudy. It's very lovely. It's very chic, isn't it? It's a very
It's a new muscle Messiah
Yeah, I love it. Come on guys. You know I am German. I can do my arms.
Like that Hamas. Oh shit.
Oh my Lilith is coming out tonight.
Oh shit. Lilith is coming out at midnight.
She's already here. Well she's actually here a few weeks early.
We'll talk about the doll Lilith, the one slob that like dances on the bed.
Oh the actual Lilith the goddess of the earth.
Oh, you're talking about that one.
Oh, Lilith.
No, Lilith was the very first feminist.
The first feminist.
OK, I'm going to play the Lilith song.
She's like the mother of all the demons or something.
Yes, yes.
No, she's not.
She's the first feminist.
There's nothing to do with her being evil.
You're thinking of the Lilith fair.
The Lilith fair you're thinking of.
No, I'm talking about Lilith, whatever her name is.
goddess home i'll play the song yeah goddess here's a little song she was a very she was the
very first feminine that's feminist that's where i heard she was made out of the earth and then
eve came along she was made out of adam's rib but lily's was made out of the earth uh oh well here's
But shim
She feeds on shit
That's beautiful.
Thank you.
I love this one too.
It's biographical.
I'm sorry guys.
I don't know how I got so drunk off of it.
I finished my, I missed it but I have weed coming.
When's the weed coming?
You're drunk right now?
Yeah, too hard of a minute.
But it's on that and on sadness too.
But it's fine.
Yeah, and you don't have any weed in here.
When you have solid alcohol and you're not reading it too,
it's like you get so drunk
because you don't have the weed to balance you out.
I know what it's like.
I've been there.
I'm gonna eat my last cheeseburger.
Look at this.
All I've eaten in the last three is McDonald's.
Look what it did to me.
It drove me insane.
I mean, I think there's too much human meat in the burgers. I'm not sure.
Maybe it's Matt Kel's disease.
It's very angry cow, personally. I mean, it's called mad lol cow disease.
Yeah, mad lol cow disease. That's utterly funny.
I'm kind of funny.
Hopefully 20 minutes. Let me see. I know I know what it's like when you're waiting for your Wii to come
It's like the worst time in the world
It is I'm ready to smoke it I'm ready to smoke some I'm meaning a vape at 11. Yeah
It's been a hard day. It's not a hard day, but
I'm okay. I'm okay. Yeah
Or that or that trip to get it it's like it's I don't know why the trip to the weed store takes like for fucking ever
But no other store ever takes as long as it takes to get to a weed store in Canada
We have weed stores and I don't buy it on the street anymore because I'm scared of vent
So I buy it at the store. Yeah, because they won't put the fence is too expensive for them. It just makes it in the store
Right right need cool extras of the store but the store. Justine shut up. Yeah
I'm good, how are you good? I'm glad you're good
I'm very I do I miss you. I miss you a lot. You know, mr. God. I know I've heard you crying lately. I
Do I cry?
Have you been baking?
Yes, I have I just made a cake. I'll show it to you guys. If you want me to be here be here. Oh
God he loves cake
What's that? What do you say if you want me to be here beyond like tonight?
I need your help. Just to like be here. What do you need? Just to be here. Just to be, I don't need any help. I mean, just like, just like moral support. Yeah, we're here for moral support.
Moral support against what? See?
Oh, it's like everything's happening. Everything's happening to me. But I'll be back. I'll be back.
Is that cream cheese
No, it's no, it's no, it's just buttered icing. What kind of cake? I just with this. It's just vanilla
What up, dude? I just made a plain vanilla
No, it's good. I like vanilla
And just vanilla icing
I would eat it sometimes. That's all you need in life. Just a vanilla cake. Hey, what's up, bro?
I was Mike is busted
It's real vanilla
Sometimes I drink it. I'm just you're like a wizard. Justine in the kitchen. You're a wizard
You're like Martha Stewart
Betty Crocker, I do love cooking. I like it. I whip that cake up without even a recipe
Love cooking so much baking. Is that real flit of diamond or is it porn bomber?
I never know anymore
I'm both. Thank you very much. That is true. That's true. Yep. Yeah, I'm both
Don't do it. Don't do it to me. Hi flirty diamond. I've never met you, but hi. Nice to meet you
Nice meeting you. Nice meeting you nice meeting you flirty
People I like I'm mad. Oh, I met her and like passing
Was it good or bad?
Don't know. It was more like a high-five. Oh, okay. Yeah
Cool, justine justine. Oh, justine. Yeah, I've never met flirty, but
Say hi to psych. Yeah, no
He's left easy
Dick and far fish taco
Hey, you know, you know, me, I'm always keeping it very real, you know, buried the mirror.
I love that. I love girls with a sense. We love to be around here.
Yes, like you can come up.
What happened to your neck cuz I gotta go suck some dick cuz my fish taco just came
Because my fish taco just
I don't blame him. A girl gotta do what a girl gotta do in the world.
You do, baby! Yeah, you gotta do what you gotta do! You gotta hit what you gotta hit!
You got it all so good guys. You got it all so good
Paritos you don't do fish tacos no more psyches
No, I turned into a fish taco and then I've turned into a fish burrito and then man
It definitely gets wild. I guess everybody's just converting into something now. It's really going so crazy. Hey, by the way, I the best show on YouTube
Why are there only 22 people here?
We need, everyone in the chat needs to share the stream right now.
It's cause Sam-Man.
I didn't know there were people that Sam-Man playing, you know, attend to him.
Please, please, please.
Go to Sam-Man's and say go to Psyche's, please.
Can someone do that, please?
Go to say why did why does salmon have had it on salmon for like a second or two?
I had to tell my old fleeing good night. Hi. Hi
Why does salmon have tits? What if I want, you know, what if I wanted to be
This is the best show on YouTube
By the way, look for the CFF. We have Flurry Diamonds. We have, I'm here too. I mean,
click on here. It's my show. I'm here. You're CFF. You're CFF too, honorary.
Yeah, I'm an honorary. You're gonna share on YouTube. Thank you.
Justine's the CFF mascot. No, not no more.
Yeah, you are justine
I got kicked off of that bill. Anyways, it doesn't matter. Well, you're still reapplying. So we're still accepting applications
I move forward. I really yeah. Yes, like you are the high priest. I move forward. We have a hundred percent
I move forward sideways backwards I go up down
You're fucking funny as shit, chick. I love you. I'm I'm controversial. That's why I don't go.
Saigi doesn't want me up here because I'm too controversial for people. Oh, I do.
Why? You're funny as shit. If people don't understand your humor, tell them to grow a
Fucking
Diamond is that funny bones a lot of people that were like anti-trans and then it's like
Because like I got pregnant
Show or this YouTube show I got pregnant by like 20 people and then like I took a bunch of plan B's and then like I
At least you were smart 30 diamond was the first man to have I wasn't that I wasn't smart though
Cuz I could have collected child support. I could have collected all the
Yeah, you don't ask you forgot about the child support. I know
Support first
I just know I I shook up too many people cuz I was just too
I don't know. I'm just an old name, but I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not
That's a Jerry sign felt you could have had
Failed I don't there's no such person. It's Jerry Seinfeld. Oh
Jerry Springer because he had that stupid show
Springer psyche is like the YouTube of Jerry Springer
I'm like Jerry Springer, Howard Byrne and Fulverly Diamond had a baby and that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's
I would just, I don't know. I'm bored right now.
Yes.
Are you sure?
Let me see.
No.
Why do I have to show you my toilet?
Because every time I talk to you, I have to see it now.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I'm hot.
I didn't have to do anything.
I have to inspect that shit.
Pun intended.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It is not.
Don't be rude. I saw the dude do these things.
Oh my god.
I don't know what the red balloon right now right now you can't make it to the
bathroom why oh my god do you know what the red balloon is from it no
It's because I had a sugar daddy on here and point as I exposed them on here and
They they will put a red balloon over his penis
No
No, it's not one of those two
How many guys you have for it? I mean goddamn. Oh my god. This was like the oh, oh my god
No, this was this was the cause this was the most controversial one
Yeah, everybody would everybody would say who's holding the red balloon and he was holding cuts
They would put a red balloon over his penis
God.
RIP.
Remember when you made, like, the, um, the Bartome and Bailey
switch with them under your, um, your dress?
And I got in trouble?
Wait, I went, oh, the beat box.
Yeah.
You put it all in the second thing.
It was all in the second thing.
Oh, my God.
No, that was the real deal.
That was, like, the real, real deal, you know?
Guys best show on YouTube by the way. Hey guys, you know, I love you so much and you know what everyone up here
I love don't really don't love our people that are like, you know mean and you're like all kind
Thank you. I mean, I'm nice
I'm everything. Well, I I'm bipolar for a reason, you know, minus the by part. Yeah, she's just polar. I just I am strictly dickly
He's more polar than the earth. She has more than two poles. She has three
You know what I am I have ADHD
for real
I
Ad and that's really offensive to me a dick
Ad ad that's not
Yeah
Oh, I thought you said Edie
Everything
Videos that one's trading. You know what everybody in here they get something
Yeah, I'm not promising if it's good or bad, but they definitely get something
Definitely an experience for sure for sure. I have something something I have is
Everything everything is I'm gonna show you guys you guys check my week's almost here. How many minutes ten minutes?
If you guys don't know what it's like to be a pot smoker and have your weed so close to you, it's like, it's like, it's like, you get into your brain. That's all you think about is pot. How much more minutes, how many more seconds, or how many more kilometers, am I going to have to go to get pot? It's really crazy.
Oh, no
But I really like crazy first people, you know, I'm a little crazy myself
We like your eyeballs what the fuck
I have two of them
No one else got it. I was going to ask. What are you talking about? I have three nights.
I have all my mouth right now. He thinks this is a glory hole right now. That's why his
I love you chick. You are a funny flirty girl. I like it
Alex I ain't got nothing to do with that. I
Don't even eat fucking burritos. I don't eat nothing. I start myself every day
You believe that that's not very nice
So I put her on the list, you know what listed is it's Santa's naughty list shit. It's Christmas cold
Why'd she say it because I can't help myself
Phone oh my god, why is acting up?
God he's out playing on the fucking phone why why what I'm doing something
Okay, so I when I was like four years old I was calling the I was calling the the AT&T
I just press zero and she's to be like hello AT&T
I'd be like fuck you operator and then I pick up the phones are ringing and I picked up and they're like I
Was like hello, and are you that nutty little boy telling me to go fuck myself?
Sorry
Yeah, the first time I bring up the hook, and she's like, oh, no.
Yeah.
And then she's like, well, I like your friend.
I like your friend, Florie.
Isn't she cool?
Florie Diamond's cool.
Yeah, Florie is fun.
What happened to your neck?
She had to go.
She had to go for a second.
She had some kind of something.
I'm right back.
What happened to your neck?
Someone slit it.
Someone slit my throat.
No, it's very veiny.
It is veiny, because I'm veined.
Oh, you are being. Yeah, that's true. You're so
Nails justine what got terrible nails you want to see them
the
Am I in the cares? No, I just just petty people. No, no, I know
You want to know something I've seen Tom Petty in concert
I've seen Tom Petty in concert for when the heartbreakers and Pemberton and in on in British Columbia, Canada
You did
You don't understand I have loved Tom Petty since the 70s. I know I'm old I'm old. I don't even know who that is
One more time to kill the baby and it's like, um, what is what is the Alice in Wonder slaw?
Come on, it's also wonderland under Alice in Wonderland was a slot. She was getting fucking ran through by
He gives it up stop fucking
Gives it up stop go wait in any
Alex I don't fucking like Otto Otto's fucking
Otto's retarded. He's literally retarded. I don't I don't like repart. I mean, I don't like rerease. Let me be um
Let me be nice. I don't like re-rees.
I don't like re-rees. I also fucking re-ree.
I don't like re-rees.
And he's fucking dumb and he has a small dick.
Oh yeah. You know, if he's dumb and has a small dick, you don't want him at all.
Girl, all he can afford is fucking condoms from Planned Parenthood.
They're free god, I don't give a fuck. I'm not gonna have a condom break and then get pregnant. Thank you very much
I don't have a condom. I have a condom. I only carry magnums
I'm not type of girl and that's my life
Those are supposed to be for the guy not for you. I don't need I love cuz I know I need a man that fits a magnum
Thank you very much. No girls go out with condoms in their purse when they go out
Fuck you. You got it. You thought I had your free time on them actually because what if you like you go to talk about your dumb woman?
Auto is a very sad sad mexico. Look auto is a
We we don't we don't claim him. We don't claim them. Who has autos um something y'all should tell him to join
It'll be a reunion and then I can pound her and we're done
I don't know. That was funny though when Otto joined. That was a really funny day.
Otto, come up here if you're around. Otto, come on.
We do not claim him.
I don't claim him either. I have a man in real life, so I don't claim him.
Hey, Fergie, I would suck your dick. Hey.
Oh my God. I should show Otto my dildo. I own two of them.
You should. You should just scare him off.
No, here's the thing though with fucking Otto, it's like, he was, he, Otto's convinced that he's like the shit, like, he thought that everyone wanted his, like, little pecker and not like, summer was trolling him, I was trolling him, and it was, it was funny, we got him to bark like a bitch.
Oh my god, you did remember he was rubbing lotion on his like naked body. I guess um Alex is um auto's man now
Alexander you're my man. Well, I guess you got cheated on psyche. There you go. Shit. Yeah, man
I only pay for that in the show on me
They the psyche I just fucking I'm sorry. I caused you to get cheated on by coming up here. I'm sorry
We'll give you baby wipes too. Oh my god, I need to see some laughter the chat guys
Just see that was so fake. Come on. Come on. That was the most fakeest laugh and it was just
That was faker than autos
Visual belief of his own dick
Yeah, it is faker than the auto bond
You know I have implants just like um other people
Thank you. Nah. I'm kidding. I'm not gonna be caught. I have implants. Unfortunately, they're all in my brain
I have implants like I have um triple abs
They're a fake good than my hip
They're a fake good than my butt
That's like my GPA, great triple F's
I have a fake hip
I have a fake ass
I have fake tits
I have fake lips
I have fake nose
I actually do have a fake nose
I do, I got a nose job when I was 17
by Jane Fonda's Plastic Surgery
Yeah, you got that white privilege
and you got a nose job
You got a white privilege alone
I'm sorry, I don't have all my privilege.
That's fucking funny.
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wait, privilege.
Well, you know what?
If I got so much white privilege, then why am I so poor?
BAM!
I'm not poor.
Because you didn't know how to do the cheat code.
You entered the wrong cheat code.
You have to use it right.
You know white is right you can be you gotta like you gotta like be seen and then you gotta just like
Well, I'm gonna put my cash up in the chat time. It's just cuz you you don't you don't suck dick for fish taco burritos. That's why I
Shot goes not for two
Yes, like that's that's a cheat code. I never make a man pay for sex
I never treat a man like an ATM because
Men have souls. No, they don't. Men don't have no souls. Men have people. Men are people too, you know.
No, they're not.
I'm gonna start a fucking show. I'm gonna fucking start a show and I'm gonna call it men are people too.
Oh my god, you're a pig. You're a pig, Nisha. That's what you are. You're a pig, Nisha.
Most men are players and eventually when they get bored and they have no more cards to play
That's when they settle. Well, men are players but for you diamond. I are the coach. Okay, so I rather play
I rather play a funner game
Which is called
I rather play I
Rather play this lovely game called what's the ATM limit? I the biscuit
Yeah, that's my favorite game. It's literally called. How far does this card go?
What's the digits?
I weed almost here. What do you see?
It's like, yeah, men just stay cheat. They really do be cheating.
I just never really had a very many men cheat on me.
I had two men cheat on me, but they haven't really cheated on me.
You may have cuz men do they do be secretive some of them don't give a fuck don't cheat right in front of your face
You're secretive. Oh, how about secretive women are so secretive men don't even get it
They think the woman's being obvious and she's got she got him by the balls the whole time
But that's another man. I have my husband by the balls. You're married. Oh my god
I'm very lucky to be actually married in real life you're my fiance. I'm really upset now psyche. We were never married
We're divorced and you're not getting half my shit
Thank you. You don't have shit to take
Let's just add the point. Okay, you know, thank you. I'm taking this
Do you mean it's my pussies? I'm taking your cats. I'm sorry. Oh, you cannot have them. You know what you get bad
That's all you got to your name. Yeah, my fish taco fun
It's like I don't want your fish tacos. I mean it's rock says I'm starting my own
Women get money from men, but men should get pussy payments from their wife because you know because they're you know
Because the only thing that a woman has to give in the marriage is their pussy
Marriage anything it's it's simply a transaction on because at the same time a woman isn't gonna put out tall man as proof
But himself and that's typically going on dates. I've typically evolved spending some type of money
So eventually a man who rather but still rather just buy a hoe then like deal with all that
I want to buy a shovel not a hoe because I don't
And I'm gonna be like 12 feet deep in the ground that would be lovely. Oh my god, not my feet
I'm kidding
Okay, but no, it's his men cheat. Munchie. You just got to pick. You got to pick a man, but there's a lot as much. Women cheat, but they don't hear his calls.
You can go with his past.
It's called suspicion, and women don't get suspicion, but they're doing everything.
I don't know who James Craig is.
He's just Jenny Craig's younger, slimmer brother.
I'm young. I'm like in my twenties.
You are yeah 21 years old. She's basically hardly allowed to be here. I'm always gonna be 21
I will always be 21
I will never get older in life
I will never do nothing but be 21 and that's my that's my life goal the fountain of youth and
I discovered that like I
Know the fountain of youth. It's called Botox and filler
Yeah, I thought it was semen, but okay, that's fine.
A semen.
You know, some of us are like facials, some of us don't like facials.
Yeah, I don't get, hey, I don't get Botox.
I bet get Botox.
I get Botox instead of Botox.
If you just have a moment of being just being,
it's not being funnier than me.
Man.
I like to be the host.
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just
My god, that's sorry guys. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Oh my god. He's finally going to get his way
Make sure that you put on your tiniest skirt so you can be able to get a discount
Yeah, exactly
Or put on your American speedo
Yeah
That's how you get a good discount, you know
I know I used to go and get pot and I used to look sexy because I used to be you know this
I used to like try to get you know, this than that and I used to get free pot all the time
I mean yeah, cuz I mean it's not pretty
Yeah, that's I mean that this call being a woman, you know, I've never really except for having now because I had to buy a vape because I can't do real pot in my house.
So it's cost money. So I had to buy myself low and he doesn't agree with vaping. He thinks that you should just smoke the wheat, the flour.
Your husband doesn't let you smoke weed.
No, I don't have a husband and I don't why I have been engaged a lot. I just don't want one.
Wait, so who doesn't let you smoke weed then I I in my building. I cannot smoke
Proper weed like they like real marijuana. So I think they ain't gonna know
Yeah, they will because I live right opposite my landlord. So he will smell why don't you babe?
Because that's what I'm doing. I'm vaping
But he doesn't agree with vaping because he thinks it's bad for you. How's he gonna know about vaping?
Well, because he I don't know he just doesn't he won't give me like he won't buy fate
So he doesn't give me faith
Get it
Man, I just I'm trying to understand this this is to my brain can process it. I'm
I'll smoke whoever and I'll I'm just a hood rat. So I don't know what else
Farted and left
That was gaudy.
Did we just get crop dusted?
Not by me, but probably by gaudy.
Yeah, one second.
I'm going to say the test.
We really just got crop dusted.
What's crop dusted mean?
OK, I can hear shit now, so I'm going to restart.
Like the lingers, the lingers around the people's
nose.
I'm sorry, that was too bolder.
Oh my god, I was right.
OK, hold on one second.
Hey, you know what, Florida Diamond, thank you for being my friend because you're fucking
a badass.
If people didn't get it before, they're going to get it now because you're a badass.
Hold on.
Oh, she's back.
Hold on a second.
Yeah, last thing I heard was like a crop dusting noise and then like
That was gaudy just talking. Yeah, that's the last thing I actually fucking heard
It was like a fart noise and then someone left and I was like damn
We got crop dusted and then I couldn't hear nothing else on here. I was like, oh wow
Hey, mr. Alexander, I am not beta. Sorry I know Alexander used to be my boyfriend. Oh
Yeah, but then I couldn't handle him no more. He was too small
You know, I should know how Alexander looks in real life because like I I saw his reflection in the mirror of a car
That's not here nor there
Used to be very controversial with me. I
He said some he says some things you shouldn't have said before but
People think I sound like beta do I really sound like her
And these lashes on fucking match
Did I really just lose my fucking one pair of matching fucking lashes?
Do you want to know something embarrassing?
I'll tell you something really embarrassing.
I had two very, very, I can't hear shit again.
The fuck is wrong with the stringard app?
I can see like that just seems talking, but like I can't hear nothing.
Yes, who's back? Look at it. I got one.
Hey, Lola.
Yeah, I got to start again.
Fuck this fucking app.
Okay, look at what I got. Justine are you there? Look at that. Look at that. See look what I got. Look what I got
Oh here she comes. Oh here she comes. 30 damn
I don't know
She's a man
I don't eat man. I don't eat a man
You see him see man. Hold on. No, I asked I don't need one man's ass though. You asked man
You asked man. Hey, thank you. Do you ask? I would have anyone wanted me to eat it, but nobody wants me to
Here's Lola. I
Can I can say you have this like lovely guy. She's more than from universe and he likes this ass a psyche
Who doesn't I mean
I mean literally eating it
He's a good friend of mine, he's a good friend of pads he likes to ask a you might know him I think
His name is yeah, yeah, okay. Yeah, I know yeah, I think
No, he isn't oh my
No, okay. No, oh god. No
He's controversial, but
Do you know
Hey, oh my of course, I know her she made a whole segment about me. She said that Zea was my trafficker and
So was pebs
No, pebs is the one with the money and the car
I knew it. Yeah, peps used to take me on the blade and like she would like
Shoot she told me to make her $10,000 tonight
And then she broke out with me and then she ran off into the sunset with they and then she left
They at the desert and then she ran off again. What happened to $10,000 though?
Where's the $10,000? Can I have it? She got herself a damn BPL in Tijuana. Oh my god
Fucking peps of the genius mastermind. No one ever looks at peps always Zaya
Pebs is a mastermind come on guys. I'm just kidding pebs. I like I love pebs. She's great
I haven't seen her really she was really sweet to me. I do appreciate her because she was nice
I've never heard of her. She was on the Flintstones. Her name is Pebbles. Oh, yeah
When I was a little girl, I had a cop with the Flintstones. I had Betty rubber Betty rubble if I can speak
And I had a big book of my last time I never I'm sorry time. I told you last time I
Ended up donating your hair to someone. That's actually for myself. I need my ass hair to start growing back
So I used it for a trans flat
Yes, I stole time's hair and I ended up getting an ass hair transplant so I can never give
Dime their hair back again because I ended up getting a transplant for ass hair
Do you clean that ass hair with real poo? Oh my god, you don't clean it with that you
It's because time call me a ball headed hoe a couple months ago because time found out that I wore extensions
So I told and then time thought I still hair from them
So I told him like you saw that hair for an ass hair transplant and I don't know how time feels about it
But that's how it is
I'm called me a nappy headed hoe too. You're a jerk time. You're really a jerk. I just
It was it just what happened in the moment like I just I got I got sad cuz like I saw Psyche's photo and him and his
Beato, and I was like
Yeah, I saw all your ass hairs that you psyche I got jealous so like I ended up having to get an ass hair transplant
And I use thymus hair for it because we're competition now, you know
I know I needed that luscious thick hair
I knew that Brazilian 30 inch bust down ass hair.
Yeah. Fuckin' hell. Let's play some McGruff character across the country for McGruff.
McGruff?
Police fighting dogs.
Nah, I'm kidding.
I know. I was serious. I was being serious.
Just ignore me. I'm just...
Your follicular teeth?
No, I love it. I love your stick.
Just ignore me. It's like, it's 1.20 in the morning. I'm hilarious.
I'm a dick. I'm a dick.
No, man, I like your shtick. Where is it? I like it. Why is the whole chat and the panel left? I mean, I don't understand
You know, I went to I went to a salmon set and guess who the only person I saw talking there was
Beat is kitty gang
I'm in the Barry and Kate gang. That's what my BKG sounds like
Yes, darling
I don't even know. I don't have a comment.
No comments? Oh, please comment. I want to hear your comments.
I don't know nothing and I'm not getting invited.
I don't know nothing either. I don't know nothing either, okay? I don't know.
I'm still confused. I'm still confused.
Man, lick her pussy and make up already. I don't know.
Hey, IP2 Lambda, Lombada.
Get me on IP2 and have them read this stream right now. Let's get 100 people in here tonight, okay?
Let's do it. Let's fuck it. Fuck this shit. I'm ready. I'm ready.
you got your pot you're ready for it I really don't know what happened what
what do you like to use I just I have no comment I have no comment either but I
do have a comment
In hell, no, his dick is fucking small. He has a fucking want he has a wonky eye
He scratches his ass and then he fucking sniffs it right after
We're about to be rated by IP to and I probably get on it tonight because I actually did lose my shit
Finally just took a little bit of a little you lost your shit earlier psyche. Yes, I did
I'm proud of you. You finally do for the first time psyche
Guys, let's be Sandman playing little nightmares and how about like me fucking purging crashing
Whatever fucking word you want to say something's happening. Okay. Let's just do it. Let's run this shit. Okay. Go ahead
We're gonna run this town. We're gonna run YouTube. I'm gonna be the CEO next, okay?
You hear that whatever yes
Yes, ghost ghost overcast guys by the way ghost
I'm having another thousand dollar month on YouTube. Thank you ghost. Thank you ghost. I won't forget you
You make me laugh till your face turns blue your funny outrageous. You sure are a bless
This moment like me. Why did you crash out earlier?
Because beta told me to unalive myself and that was that was all I needed to hear
whoa psyche what did you what oh my oh god what's the backstory behind this just
that she's a psycho and then she wants gay people okay but when did you guys
start arguing again in April we've been arguing since April so I got monday
okay but like what's the most recent argument
When I said I texted her say I miss you. I hope we can work things out
I love you as a friend and then she said never contact me again
Go and all this other shit. So yeah, and how many days went by since you contacted her after?
Well, I mean that was just this morning. So it's very recent
So when did you guys last talk?
Like before that person if we're all I went on our show with my wig and I thought I was vegan Patriot
But I think she actually believed I was vegan Patriot as she was like really confused
Oh God, I don't even know it too. Oh my God.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
If you think you're confused, think about how confused I am.
I mean, fuck, cause I don't like shit.
I mean, you guys weren't getting along a couple weeks ago.
Like when I, when auto shit happened, I know that, but like.
I try, I mean, it's like, it's like more up and down than, you know, sex with you.
I mean, it's, it's.
Y'all just need to like go to therapy with each other and just, I don't know.
Wait, hold on, wait.
OK, I know you don't like Alexandra, but I do want to show you a couple of things.
Alexandra, I don't like her.
She doesn't like me, psyche.
OK, well, I'll talk to her.
You know, I met her.
She said I had HIV and she said I had HIV and she said I was out here doing everything in the world.
I get pulled out of these other times today that I had HIV.
You know what? We don't have HIV.
She said I was an HIV hooker that was giving all these men HIV and everything.
Okay, well, I want to show you a couple of things. Okay, I don't know what her problem was but IP to wiki.info
This is one of her sites and so she made a few
Really good AI. I'm on her side. You're on the side. Okay, so I'm gonna
Think that is I love you, but I think it's funny that she posted some pictures of you
So think of who?
Think that is all I turn off my a my a background wait who does he post you know thing that is
He's a mind control expert. He's like MK ultra trainer. That's on my show. I don't know. Nobody's psyche. I'm literally
Well, this is him, right here. Oh
It's a good here's him
Is he on drip? I mean is he on
I love you think this thing that is in the chat. Okay, and it says imagine imagine being this triggered by an Alex
Hold on and this is Alexander and Alexandra. Okay, because I think Alexander picks them up
They're they're kind of but they're they're cute. Okay, and then this is the one
That way there's me as a priest look
You see
Well, she made you really short thing that thing that is you're not like a dwarf. Are you I mean that'd be funny
Cuz I'm really tall. Maybe I'm just so tall
It's just imagine having to do with a frequent panel guest who takes issue want to know something psyche
Alex and my PD. It's really Alexandra. Oh my god. It makes so much sense. It really does make sense
Okay, but look at this for you. I mean look imagine
So
Who is that?
I know, I know like Zandra, she like pretty much was doxing beta, but I know beta's been
kind of doxed already, but I know she was partaking in that.
She can be doxed if you've already been doxed, because doxing means your information is put
out.
You can't it doesn't mean it's out for the 10 millionth time and everyone already knows it
I know it's just another day when it comes to Alexandra. She has no
boundaries and no
Listen, you know what?
Person like you have boundaries for diamond. I mean really I think about I don't talk to people. I don't do shit like that
Okay, but I know, but look it I want to show you a couple more. I didn't have boundaries. I don't talk. I don't um
Maybe but but sorry diamond. What if someone is fucking really what if someone tells you to go unalive yourself?
I don't care. I'll literally send them a video. I'll send like a video of someone that already self-harmed and I'll send them the photo of him
I'll make them feel bad and I'll traumatize them like that. Well, but if they're making those kind of stress
They're probably not very easily traumatizable. They're probably already kind of psycho. I mean, I mean I got
I don't think you should be telling people to analyze themselves. Don't get me wrong, but at the same time
I
Not me. I mean come on. We're talking about me here. I know that's what I mean
I don't I don't believe in telling people to analyze themselves. I'm just
I've been told to on the line myself thousands of times and I just I stopped giving a fucking life
I know and trans people will be told that and I
That's the thing with life. I said you got to stop giving a fuck about everything cuz like every day, you know
Okay, but the end of the day this is the best picture. What is it things like?
Y'all got married psyche. Yeah, I'm married. He married you guys psyche. We did
Beautiful it was that's not yeah, and she told y'all got married. She told you I'm not live yourself the next day
Married us psyche. It's because you didn't give her no dick the next day
I taught her trying to cut it off, and I was like, um, no, thank you when you get married
You're supposed to give a woman thick and you can convert you I be too long Bada. Wait, there's 10 people 10 more people here
What's with that? Where's that be two people? I need I need some like fucking again. Oh, okay 30. Okay 37. Okay. We're doing good
Okay, it's I don't know psyche
I don't believe you anymore. You're not a part of IPG. IPG would have people here.
Saki, did you, were you cheating? I feel like you cheated on her.
On who?
I feel like you were cheating during your honeymoon.
With Bita?
No, I feel like you cheated on Bita and when you're on the honeymoon.
But I wasn't, but...
Bita only forged my signature to appear that we were she forced your sick psyche
Yeah, I feel like she had a 10,000 fish taco burritos
There's like a fucking hit man knocking on my door right now for her. It's like fuck go away
I'm not gonna like you. She had she promised you 10,000 fish taco burritos and now you feel like she
Like you was 10,000 lies. It was just 10,000 lies you told me. Yeah, but psyche you felt for these 10,000 burritos
I don't really fall for them because I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have my door locks right now, I fell for them when I have
What do I expect Mary? I'm a fly trying to marry a black widow.
It's not going to work out well. I just, but you know what?
I'm super fly. I'm super fly. Not, not a super SEP.
Oh my God. Y'all I'm actually so cool that I'm almost black.
Okay. I can even rap a little Kim.
I think you're not black. You had black in you. There's a difference.
Exactly. I had a black guy in me once. It was great. It was great.
Never again, but it was great.
Why never again? Was it too big for you?
Yes, it was um, what's up? I know this guy his name session and oh, he's Mexican
He's kind of like a little bit special
But he has a condom some flambent hood and like I think you and him what that wig I think you guys are like
I don't have a paid pizza, man. The fact that you have to emphasis on the word paid
Why do you pay for the manure? It's like not that much. She was like, you know, $3 a bag and stuff
And you have like 10 bags delivered
Can I do your makeup and can I like fix your wig?
Yeah
When if I ever go back to California, I'll I'll I'll Sissy find you
Okay, if I ever go back to California I'll Sissy fight you and you'll be the best to see in the world
I'm a hot blonde bombshell
Psyche, that's not blonde, that's white.
Hey, where are you diamond?
Do you know my last name is Bates?
I'm going to talk to myself.
My last name is Bates.
I know, we're friends on Facebook.
Right, and do you know who Norman Bates is?
Who?
He was in the movie Psycho, and...
His mother was like the corpse in the house that he was like saying was his mom
Okay, so sounds like your name is cursed and you need to get married to a man with a different name
In the name masturbates my last name is in the name masturbates. That's what I'm actually really blessed. Oh my god
Radio I am it's like I get so much white light all the time. It's crazy. You're like the next RuPaul of YouTube
Right because RuPaul's on a very good drag queen, right? It's like
RuPaul RuPaul RuPaul is not even has enough as balls cut up
I mean come on no cuz like RuPaul can't like do his own makeup or nothing. I'm like
I
Don't want to be able to do my own make I want to be able to pay people to do the makeup because it's much trouble for me
To sit there and do I can do your makeup
Okay, well I'll pay you to do it
Yeah, fuck it. I'll go back to albacca go back to LA
I can't I I can't I can't fly me out there then. I'll have to work it off. Oh my god. I'm too poor
Well, it's not going to work out for you, Diamond.
No, I just, no, I just got caught up in a thing.
You're going to have guys begging me for a year,
and then you'll see like, oh, I'm going to.
Oh my god, Psyche, you're telling me to pin you out on YouTube.
I'm not with auto, but like it's really. Oh my god. Everyone. I'm psychies pimp now. I'm gonna be I'm gonna be pimping out
Tacos
And when they come to the house and have beat them up, we're gonna beat them up sealer wallet
Drug them and then put them on like the I don't do those type of things
You're just gonna have to do what you got to do
Alright, it was like a private girl, I didn't teach you to do that.
Oh my god, what is wrong with these psychies? Oh my god.
Y'all psychies the next like Cardi B.
Psychies trying to be like the movie hustler.
What is this song called like wet ass pussy?
I got a big ass butt and a wet ass pussy.
Psyche, you're really here saying that you're going to set up, man, that's crazy.
Psyche, I have a few names for you then in this movie.
In this movie that is going to be produced one day, I have, I know some lovely characters.
So for German, I don't want to be like I don't want to be your victim though. It's like and you're gonna try to do something to me
I don't like it
It's me. I just make a deal beforehand. We won't like eat me for dinner or something. Oh, what?
psyche
You're not gonna eat my balls and put them in a souffler psyche. I like black men. I I like black guys
That's my balls. Just promise. I like black guys
Your wife you're gonna beat me
You're white. I like black guys black eyes. Oh my god. No, I like men that are black
I like
Took a really dark pigment paint or like a like a mud mask and I put it on my face. No
I have my I have my own personal BBC that's locked up right now. I can paint it black. I do I have a big
It's not the same psyche my my own personal BBC
He's locked up right now
I don't even see the color. I'm gonna put it the room will be dark. The room will be very dark. I'll be dressed in a panda bear
No, psyche. I can't
Psyche we're not compatible. I'm sorry
But you can be my beard, all right?
We can run off into the sunset.
I want to tell nobody that you're really gay and that, like,
you really just want to get, you really, like,
going to glory halls and everything.
Because, you know, I know the world is going
to be scary again, I know.
Can you leave our glory, our glory
halls stories are going to private?
OK.
I don't want everyone to know.
Like, they did.
OK.
But we have a glory hole for you to have a nice order of glory. Oh, it's in the Nebraska. I have yeah
I have a glory hole set up just for psyche so he can be with a service everyone and then
I like I don't want to spit in the face. I want someone to hawk a luke in my eyeball
It's like, you know starting out guys rodee the nice for a generous amount of $10
Is a chat no one was a tarot reading
I mean, it's like, guys, $10 and we'll get Psyche the holler at the
Oh my God, thank you so much.
Thank you, Wiggins.
Thank you.
It's okay.
We'll have your hyperglory hole vision happen one day.
Don't worry.
Do you promise me?
Yes.
Oh my God.
Can I call you daddy?
Oh my god, we'll get you a daddy my boyfriend will pimp you out and I'll just be
As long as not auto or like anybody else. I know I need like somebody. I cannot psyche right now. I cannot right now
Oh my god, I'm dying in my craft
Oh hell oh my god, I'd rather just oh my god
I would show a photo of my mouth open, but I don't think it'll be appropriate for you to well
I got in trouble just for you rubbing a balloon animal under your skirt. I mean, I was like imagine. Oh my god
That skirt was
Beautiful
Was it was like all pumped up in the front like someone had a like a helium tank. It has to it
Thank you sometimes a girl got to do what you got to do and
Really with helium and I'll make you like a balloon and I'll fly away with you
Imagine that site I'm gonna put flurry diamond as a helium balloon with psyche being dragged by it at a 10 20,000 feet
Wouldn't that be a funny photo though or AI photo? I'm gonna do that one
Hello, I think I lost oh shit. I said too much. Oh my god
What if I don't you house j-dog then thymestead
See oh ap2 lambada. I got to thank you. I now have 57 people in the chat. Hey
He doesn't fuck around. He's true. Hey, I P2 why aren't I on you? You have there you have Victoria J
Okay, first of all this bitch doesn't even I've never been on camera second of all her photos fake third of all
She sounds like annoying as fuck worth of all her life is like like an episode of Roseanne
Okay, this bitch is on IPG before me. I've been out here for at least like eight months. Thank you fool out of myself
Trying to get on IP to and no no no. Oh, no. Oh, he's he's just like thank you. Does he haven't stuck dick on camera? That's why I
Mean Jesus Christ. I mean what else do I have to do? I've been at the pier hitting on the the fish guy
I've fucking gotten a speedo put my arms around my head like a pretzel
I've I'm sitting visiting a wig for the last month. I mean this is getting embarrassing. Okay at this point. I'm done
Psyche, you gotta go in the corner, online, but you gotta sell your ass and then you'll be fine.
Psyche, you know, wanna know Psyche? Wanna know the secret of mine?
What?
I want IP2.
You are!
No, I wanted to see your reaction.
You should be on it too!
I mean, I P2.
I only applied for I P2 like once, about a month ago as a joke.
Months.
Pretty great content.
You're like, oh, let's put it on Victoria J.
because she fights with her mom and it's kind of mildly amusing.
It's not even that funny.
It wasn't good.
I don't even know who she is, who this Victoria girl is.
Oh my gosh, she's the worst, she's like,
hi, I'm just kidding, it's gay.
Mom, don't let me do it for you in the morning.
I love you too, kind of when people
start talking about her, to be honest with you.
I mean, it's not even worth it, it's like the dumbest storyline and it's like and then I finally get to talk to her
Finally, she was on betas and so I went on betas and addresses being a patriot. You know, let me ups
Victoria jay was on the panel. I was like finally get to that's the question and just like and then as a Victoria jay
It's like being a patriot. What's up?
Silence and three minutes later. Oh, I have to go now. Bye
And then the beat is like you just came for Victoria jay. Well, duh, but
She's gonna really beat it can at least been nice to me a little bit, but and then blogger was there
It's like oh shit, I'm trying to figure out a code guys
I mean, I don't know how to code and it's not very easy to make a website from scratch
coding yourself so I have a little help with artificial intelligence but it
keeps telling me what to do then I keep telling what it tells me to do back to
it and then it tries to do it and then it tells me to do something else and I
tell them to do the same thing yeah it's a vicious cycle it's really vicious
Okay, I'm sorry. Okay. My phone. I asked me to drop it. It's okay. Um, but
I have a strap on with a phone attached to like the little roundie thing and it just fits in them perfectly
I never met this Victoria person by I heard that she argues with her
Her mom or some shit. I was just like, oh, I mean that's entertaining watch watching a white girl
Have an argument with her parents. I guess that's gonna end up dying
And she's a higher voice than Beeta.
She's like,
Hi Victoria, it's you.
And she has this like really hot like avatar photo.
You can just imagine her like 500 pounds.
I mean.
You just see it.
You just hear her in her like the tone of her voice
that she's like 500 pounds.
But she's like, oh, I have a picture of like.
fucking Alicia Silverstone or something and some AI mixed with something like hot eight in that 90s
like you know chick or something it's like it's very straight i mean it's her photo or her voice
fake or something i got i don't know much i really don't i have to find a clip one second hold on i'll
get a clip because i never heard her voice or nothing like that to be honest with you yeah she
i don't feel like going on anyone's show that's like telling me to actively unalive myself
and so i'm kind of thinking i'm done with beat it because that's a little bit too far from me okay
but anyway i'll find me toria j clip let me see if she is on ip2 i'm not she was on before me
oh i don't know sake can you email ip2 or i don't know i put myself on there i mean i've only done
a few times and you know recommend a channel say you're the channel owner and stuff they never
the presidential
Selectors, I mean, I think I don't even know it's like what do I have to do? It's like I get on the IPT down working
Well, you just have to be some kind of jitter freak. I I qualify and
Understand I'm just it really gets me down. Okay, so Victoria J. Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, did I say that out loud? Am I on camera? Hold on?
Yeah, we can see you on camera. Yeah, we're the worst of the worst on the phone, right?
This is you and me talking and no one else is aware. Yeah, no one's on the
Stream. Okay. Thank God. Why is my camera on and why am I sitting in a wig?
Thank you because you're I don't know you're drunk right now. I don't know drunk
I only had two mice her eliminates and a lot of McDonald's and I did your white girl wasted. Oh shit
Fuck you. You put on that blonde with egg psyche and you said
Girl come on. Why am I such a white girl? Okay now if it brought Victoria's justice who's a lot cooler than Victoria
Yeah, we she chose the name because she's like before injustice. That's kind of weird too because I was like, you know
Kind of like Disney Mickey Mouse Club. Yeah, but her justice that's a kiss show on
Nickelodeon
Yeah, Disney Channel Nickelodeon Victoria J. I P2 I need to put I P2 in it. Okay. There we go. I don't know
I found her a founder of Victoria J. Okay. Yeah, I don't have a real opinion about nothing y'all
I don't I mean unfortunately they were on trip. I mean they were on trip kicks, but trip kick unfortunately
One of his channels was taken down. So I have to show you her on imagine being in Janney
No, I don't really care for but I mean it's it's better than nothing. Okay, cuz I just anything to show a clip right now
Okay, oh they turn off
Hello, do you hear me for damage
Yeah, I can still hear you fine. We're okay. I'm on somewhere. Let me see. Oh, yeah, I guess I turn the browse
Okay, I'll just put this in I'm surprised Alex has some requested to go on the stream
Alexander Alexander Alex and why or did he get banned again? Oh
No, he paid his fines. He's been I can never keep up with these politics on here
Well, I just I started charging him for like because he like docs his people and then he
He like says like the racist language and he does other bad stuff and I usually will kick him off
I'm proud of you for finally charging him and making him your sugar daddy and not just your daddy
Well, yeah, I mean he's pretty he's been pretty good about I mean he bought me like one time
He bought me a crab boil and stuff like pretty much after he met me and so I mean, I wish it was like, you know
Maybe I would one dinner a week Alex and pretend like and I'll sit with you on the webcam in private and stuff
I mean, so damn, am I doing a good job? Did he pay in money or did he pay in dick pics?
He paid him he paid in
crab
You're a crab boy we went to a crab boy
That good no, no, and then he gave me also cash
The world wants to know are you picking big pigs as payments?
No, well, it's like no, I'm taking cash. I'm taking cash app and
And you know
Money orders, but I remember one Barry scammed you and you were shooketh
Well, he didn't I mean, I didn't pay anything for the for the pictures
He sent them to me like he actually offered to send them to me and stuff. Yeah, but you got a scam remember
He thought they were real everybody kept telling you
Well, I was just I was just like it was just more fun to think that they were real then like, you know
There were some you know black quarter mackerel that I've already recognized that it was Marcus. It's okay fucking I
Won't seems I won't seem very stick six
You saw it stick sick you did
How'd it look?
Was it good?
Kate cover it was only sex. It was only six it was only six so we
You know what there's nothing sadder than a black guy with the six and stick that that is like basically like basically have like one
And stick for a white guy. I mean, it's like
I want the BBC okay the BBC and I'm talking British broadcast. I want the actual BBC, okay?
Oh god, I can't have Kate come for me for mentioning his six six. Oh god. She's gonna come for me now. Oh
Lord is actually a nice person. I mean, she's not a horrible person
Actually, I'm just I'm kidding. Yeah, me too. Me too. Well, I'm not kidding. I think she's a but you like her
I do like Kate. I think but I don't want your man Kate. I'm good
Well, I mean, it's not entertainment
I'm sorry Kate, but Barry if you want to like, you know, it's a gather on the DL
I won't say I don't know nothing about Barry. I
Like his name reminds me of fruit
Don't know who Barry even is I don't know who nobody is very the turtle from I'm the careless Kate show
It used to be burying Kate. I don't know who Kate the turtle is either. I don't know who Barry the turtle is
I don't know nobody. I don't even know how I got
There's nobody in the chat right here. I think I saw him earlier. Where's nobody in the chat. Is there nobody in the chat?
Oh, it's not here right now. I'm just I'm a brand new person. I'm not
I'm a guest here. I was on YouTube scrolling and then
You're just scrolling
I was just I was literally just scrolling here on YouTube and this just showed up on my for you page and I don't know
Nobody of anything. I don't even know what a panel versus
I'll be right back. I had to go real quick. I'll be right back
Have fun. Oh god. Now. I'm here by myself
Y'all so time for us to finally pour in bomb alright
okay I'm kidding y'all man I don't know nothing about that princess that is that
is not here nor there I didn't ever have no freak off I am a child of God I'm the
Virgin Mary I had my I had my 10 birth controls or I mean can be and I I gave
First to a clownfish named Pablo
Well, let's tell y'all but anything that happened before the past I don't nothing about and that's not
Man
uh almost 25 hours out there he spurts out defending you
man i don't give a fuck about that fucking i don't care about him i really don't
he's still following me on fucking instagram he's still viewing my fucking stories
i really don't care about that shit y'all like i literally have a man my man is just locked up right now
So I'm out of town thugging with my round
I'm gonna I'm gonna become a housewife and I'm
Gonna run off into the sunset kind of
Now then I'm gonna take my online ship more serious
That was taking a serious off and then he got locked up
And then I had to do what I gotta do
So yeah
I actually do have a man though Rose like I'm for real for all the night getting married
My man is just locked up right now, but I'm gonna end up getting married and then
I want to be a changed person. I want to be a whole new person change how though
How much?
How much skin are you to put in the game?
You hear me
I'm doing anything bad done in life.
Do you hear me now?
That's the mind of ways in life.
Do you hear me?
Does anybody hear me?
That's not gonna hit.
She doesn't hear me.
Are you, is this a recording I'm talking to?
Florida, do you hear me?
I am gonna end up in a house wife.
Florida, hello.
Okay, you're ignoring me for a second.
No, I couldn't hear you, I'm deaf,
but actually my phone was messing up
a little bit back and forth.
You did?
You too the stream yard whenever I join panels like a bunch. I can't hear nobody and then I got to restart my phone. I
Thought you were just
No, I just I can don't be hearing nothing in life
Hello, hello, I didn't hear that now. I hear you though psyche. I hear you
It's who's lying burrito Alex, don't call me a burrito
I was just answering a few questions while you were gone.
Okay, well good.
I mean, anybody else have, I mean, and guys, oh, you want to link?
Which Mary?
Hold on.
My camera's just went, I've put it on high.
There you go.
But yeah, I mean.
You can talk to the chat for a sec.
I'm going to fix it.
I tell everybody how I'm living the actual street life and I'm going to housewife.
Would you oh, I know you like the the auto
No, no, I'm talking about real life. So I keep like real life. I'm actually like gonna end up being married in real life
You are
Yeah, like I'm actually in a real relationship and everything but would you it would you would leave the street life?
You know, like he's locked up right now, but well, that doesn't sound like a recipe for
Successful right now things happen in life and things happen
But he's gonna not be locked up
Like he's gonna be getting it next month and I didn't mean I didn't mean to be a dick. No, no, no
I know what you mean cuz like yeah, I mean, I thought that's what I'm not gonna be one. No gel bird
I'm not gonna be one of those like baby mama's that sit around waiting like that
Just a charge while he's locked up
You know, you're listening to you to get out of prison and the housing to make money and that's all I told him and
No, I don't got no receipts for y'all because I'm keeping this conversation between him and I actually private
I'm not doing what I typically always done, but
At this point in time though, I'm changing life around
What we're showing y'all photo of him either because I don't need y'all to know all his charges
God damn it. I don't I can't find my fucking song. I was looking for the auto flirty diamonds. I can't hear you psyche
I gotta restart okay
Okay, I'll figure out eventually I just have I only had like a hundred songs to choose from let me see
Is it this one? No, I know it's not that one. Oh
Here she comes. Oh, I said oh here she comes
Yeah, I can now I can hear you. Okay
Well, okay
Before you jay that's where we were right before you jay. I'm gonna play this one
I'll say janny. Okay. So that'll bring it right up. Okay before you show
You hear me now
Do you hear me? I can hear you my
My phone just be messing up whenever I use string yard
Okay, well, I'm gonna go to go to YouTube
Let me see.
My fucking allergies are kicking in right now.
Oh, you know what I'm saying?
Imagine me with this wig.
Okay, Victoria Ray...
Oh, she called the cops one time on...
What's the name?
Blackout Andy. Let me see if they still like that clip.
That's pretty funny.
Okay, do you remember Blackout?
Yeah, people this celebrity is...
Okay, well, I don't see the Victoria J clip with blackout Andy, but she did call the cops on him
And it was very very funny actually she called him she called his mom is like you leave you leave
He sees be oh your dex puppy on Victoria J's channel. Also. She was on vlogger. Let me I'll figure it out
I'll find one. It has to be something out there besides the Janie clip. I mean Janie. I don't think you can see but
Oh, okay. Was is there is there a channel? No, it does has 39 subscribers. Oh, okay. I found it imagine being a Janie
Okay, Bittoria J. This is only like 11 minutes. I get perfect. This is perfect. Here we go, share
Share, screen, Bittoria J. Okay
This is it. Yeah, here it is
You guys know one thing that I f***ing love, Jenny. I f***ing love Imagine Being a Jenny. Oh
Oh, my name is Imagine Being a Jenny!
Having shows RV and is ready to roll
I'll do a video later, but just for you guys right now Danny pop the curtain
Hold on. Let's do a big reveal
The problem was here while astros here we can clarify something that Victoria J was talking about earlier. Did you guys sleep in the same bed?
While you guys were staying,
well, I don't know the answer to this answer.
I'm not interested right now in your way bitch.
Why are you so scared?
So I didn't remember about me and Francis asked you a question.
Let Francis talk to him bitch.
You ain't got a reason to entertainers.
This died is for entertainment.
Die purposes.
And you've been talking about it literally before you're ruining
your show baby.
I'm going to right now.
It's set.
Get it. Get it going. Get it going.
That's why you're laughing out all the people who want attention from don't get it too big because she does not
I'm gonna say one more time. Yeah three minutes at all. Yeah, I can't I can't I can't
I'm looking at this that I has into your channel got three minutes BTW
You will look at her if you want to talk over and you want to talk over what you're talking to Francis
You are! I don't give a fuck! I don't care, you're gonna ruin the show right now. You're gonna ruin the show right now.
Nobody cares, actually Francis, I tried. I'm asking you exactly
She's like a little kid. She doesn't want to talk to people she goes after to have a voice, Lule.
It's sad that it got to that point. I was kind of hoping that it would.
Here's the thing. She started yelling first, so I yelled back. She was trying to over talk me and loud talk me because she didn't want me to expose the truth about her.
And the truth about her is that she's a liar. I'm not doing anything.
Yeah, basically.
I'm not doing anything behind the scenes. I did not dox purple. I didn't do anything. She's a liar and she wants nothing but attention. That's all I'm trying to say.
She doxed his job and that condo on stream
Okay, that's it. She has been the only one slandering me
My only question to her is why is it for okay for you to slander me?
Lyle me dox me and I'm not allowed to say anything to defend myself. Look at how she acts
You're a scary as bitch. You have all this stuff to say how you're big back tough and you're gonna
You're gonna do all this stuff. Why didn't you?
Just now. Why did you just scream into the phone and run off because you ran to Donner channel to do a panel painting views free speech
BTW everyone's been already off because you're a scary-ass bitch
So if we're gonna can so then you don't need to say anything else about me from this point on Shay
Because you had all that stuff to say when you were when you could control the narrative, right? I don't understand
I mean, it's like see how horrible it is. It's like is that interesting. I mean, it's like oh, oh
It sounds like a bunch of a bunch of white girls is arguing about shit
I mean, it's just like a bunch of whiny
Privilegeness going around
Sandy dart says I had a white I had a man whisper into my gun to one night
He sounded just like that
These people entertain the not the case people entertained I guess but I mean they don't entertain me
I mean, I do I entertain you or do they funny your ship be funny as fuck
Even if it's like they're just as funny as me. I'm so funny. I get treated like the
The shmo it is cool. Oh, it's like cuz like you always have all these in the characters on here
But it's like there's always something brand new every time. It's never like repetitive like that. I
Know I don't even know what they were arguing about. It was just so dumb
It's like I mean I would fall asleep within 30 seconds
Look that I was a what I couldn't fall asleep to those those voices, but I mean
Well, I used to fall asleep to this one typing. I mean, I think weird things are pursuing
So why why you know have she like that, you know
Yeah, and so yeah, but that no that's who they choose over me. That's who they're like, oh
The or whoever she was I decided wherever I think he's just some he's just actually Canada dry in disguise
But yeah, he's it. Oh, we're gonna
Jay on the show
insulting I
know I'm just
I
Just don't be watching drama like that
Well, let's see what's on rumble. Let me see there's blogger. They put him young. Oh god. I was posted on rumble that a day
Alexander
No, I got posted on rumble cuz I guess I'm my my life
Recorded on panel verse me too. I'm on the same thing. It's like they yeah, I didn't know I was still getting recorded by people
No, no, you will know it's again do anything about it either
But you should like like it because I should you'll keep a whole arc above your show. Yeah, my fuck it at that point
Let me I guess thank you for that point
they don't make they don't they don't monetize it and stuff and so it's like
not like they're making money and you're not it's like i mean i'm just like basically
if you're like really into the panels because they like put beat his kitties and me and like
yeah but i didn't think it was entertaining to be i haven't been on no panels in forever i'm not
active on the panel community no more well do you want to see oh so those were so five months ago
okay five months ago he was doing
a stream called the end of be this kiddies and psyche awakens I mean I haven't
watched this really recently but let me see I think I'm I think I go I go kind
of nuts in this clip but yeah so he was already five months ago I mean I'm sorry
guys is I swear this is not a story like oh shit it's worth not some kind of
storyline where it's like oh be never fighting like but five months ago we're
at the same shit was happening I don't understand this is so crazy
I thought it was also brand new with you guys to make it, but it sounds like nothing really brand new has happened
Well, why does it keep repeating itself? It's so weird. Okay, so oh people say it's a script, but I don't
Likey, do you be to make scripts with each other?
No, but I was embarrassed by what it said. So I said, oh, that was like a script, but actually
It was just what happened, but
But, I mean, I'm not, I'm not there though, I'm there for the guys.
Look at this!
The station we had was about you and like Yassine and LD15 and I said you keep doing exactly what I fucking tell you not to do over and over.
I lost your channel because of that.
I'm not crying you guys, I'm not. I'm just lost my voice.
Okay, no, it sounds like she, I'm not trying to be mean, I'm just saying she's about to cry then.
Michael, you're the one that me cry, okay? I'm not crying.
Oh my God, R.I.P.
Don't be fucking sarcastic with me.
I lost my voice because, you know,
I was like, oh, all right, Michael, let her talk, please.
OK, all right.
Hold on one second.
I mean, fuck Michael, but RIP at the same time.
Yeah, you didn't know that, Flirty?
Yeah, I know.
I've been known who was gone, but RIP,
but fuck you at the same time, Michael.
Shout out to my girl, Tracy.
Hey, do you know the thing that is?
Huh?
He's from Canada.
He's a really attractive bald man from Canada.
He's very smart.
Um
No, I don't know what it is Sandy, but it's got 51 people in it. So shut the fuck up. Okay, so here's the rest of this clip
That's another thing is like you're all right, Michael. Just shut up. Nobody even gives a fuck about your input, okay?
With all the respect the only person that really cares
When I left a few days ago, you keep saying be the comeback beta. I love you beta. This and that I said
I love you, too
I'm not coming back to the channel because I don't want to bring all that shit in here. I don't want to bring the drama
I don't want to bring and I left I was like, you know behind the scenes
I
Lied I wanted to learn over and again. I'm like psyche be careful, and I did I was fine like you know what you're not fucking listening
Yeah, I'm not going to sit there and like, listen, what were you saying when I hung up?
Are you so self-aware to realize that you know what? What I'm trying to tell you is best for you?
No. Don't fucking bring my name up. I'm bringing into this. The way you treated me in summer last
night was shit. You literally put a hand on me. Go then. Bye. Get the fuck out. You too. And yeah,
you did call me a lot of fucking names. You also said you hated me. You looked at me and you're like,
What did you say? I'm the fucking evil person and you're my fool and then you fucking kicked me like a dog.
I was being sarcastic.
Oh, you're being sarcastic?
Did you not message me like in the early mornings with a bunch of messages?
Bita, Bita, let's say it was a script.
Oh my goodness, script summer.
How do you want me to cover this shit up for you, psyche?
Yeah, we're not covering shit up no more that ship has fucking celled
I'm a real person and I have real fucking issues and I'm really fucked up in the head
So I'm really crazy. So guess what I don't do fucking scripts. I don't do behind-the-scenes shit
Thank you, can I ask you a question? What is your channel about? I've got a basic ideal myself
This is great.
It's about, you know, how many people are viewing, how much money is coming in.
He doesn't care about who was there from the beginning or end or equal.
Just, you know, every single one of us has put things out there.
I'm nothing against DJ Electra. I think she's amazing.
But last night, you literally said, DJ Electra, you're the only person that was there for me.
Like, it was like...
I said in the situation with the
And you also said I hate you, Bita.
Yep. Is that what you did?
You call me an inword. Yes you did not. I don't use that language. Yes you do when you're dropped.
Give me a clip. Give me a clip. I want to find that. That's not in my vocabulary.
You also said you told me in summer to go fucking suck Alexander and Alex Dick.
Did you ever say that?
Yeah, you wanted to suck a dick, not us.
That's my fucking brother.
I don't need a suck a dick.
You're the one on his fucking nuts and his ass wipe.
We may take out of it.
I'm pretty much done like I was like
It wasn't certain the reason I even joined last night was because I saw what was being done to summer
It was there and it also
Oh my god, five months. Look at you under the coveys. Look at you in the corner under the coveys.
right here what we have to say when you act like a baby you're just like oh i don't want to hear it
i don't want to hear it i want this i want that you throw tantrums and it's like you need this you
want to see you're turning your back just like a baby this is like you're 45 years old you're a
Oh, my God, the best part is in psyche.
This is about to get to the bottom of it.
This is their business.
It's not moving.
Are you going to delete this?
You're not going to elect her and Psyche calls it.
That's who caused it.
I don't really know.
I was in there from the beginning.
This is about one time a ghost came on
and we thought he was telling me.
Oh really? You're telling me that?
That's funny.
That's what that's what happens here. That's what happens. That's what they're bad at.
No way. Well, psyche responsible because he needs to be able to...
You're dead. You're dead. It's like a dead body. They don't even say nothing.
They could care less than you under the power.
Would you have like booted Alex NYPB app if it wasn't for the 50 dollars that Tracy provided?
He said no. Oh, god. The Tracy game.
So to me, that tells me he wanted Alex here. He wanted him despite him threatening his child.
Look at him. He's snoring.
He loves that shit.
He loves it
This is not a joke if you want to talk get up and have a little bit of respect for me and summer
Easy stay out of your mumbo mop douchebag let these three
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, I would pay a million dollars to know what's like he's thinking at that moment
Like if there was a bubble over his head like a cartoon, what the fuck would it say?
He's moving people around
Again, this is between you and me, real proud of you, real proud of you two and so, a lot of accomplishments in your life of that, huh?
Alright, well, we're not really the people that happened to in putting ghosts for all here.
So, raise your feet. Don't you let me, ghosts, and they to be the pop twins, sir.
Sir, I don't know if you look scared.
Look, I'm not scared of anybody, alright?
I just want to know what is it that you keep putting the input to I want to hear what psyche has to say
Did I say I want to hear black who has to say I said I want to hear what psyche has to say
I'm looking at a finger again, that's what he has to say.
We were in the middle of just moving him over on the board, but okay, go ahead.
I'm trying to be as respectful as possible.
I'm telling you, just let him speak.
Let everybody please be quiet.
Peter and Ghost and Summer, the ones that had the issue,
can everybody please just mute up and let us talk?
Ghost is here.
Since he is the person this is all about, can he fucking talk?
Hey, Ghost.
You know ghost and summer your summer
So as I told you all that is not Tony's voice not even close
She just put herself in the third person doing this fight look at psyche. Oh, you're not cuz it's not your fight
I did. I apologize. I was also on your panel earlier. If you're talking about today, I was on your panel. Everyone just pile up on me.
We know, but you did that after last night.
Okay. Everyone hate me. It's fine.
Nobody hates you. Nobody hates you. It was you that clearly stated you hate me last
time.
Nobody hates you. Wow, this was probably months ago.
You know, all that came out or that's how you really feel, but you said it and afterward
you were like, oops, and then you covered your mouth. You're like, I love you. I mean,
like, come on.
Join ice. Wow. This is a passive aggressive bitch from hell. We're just catching on now
You're old enough to know that those are emotional manipulation tactics when you say everyone
Don't feed him that face don't feed him when he says everybody hates me let him sit in that shit because obviously we're fucking here because we don't hate you
Duh, that's why we're here
Yeah
She did Sandy North that's why she sounds that way
Above your friends again, psyche
You know
All right
And you're having it because you wanted this kind of fucking
This is what you want it
Otherwise we get thrown on that's what we're trying to be a spread
Can ghost came up and just resolve all this right now?
I don't know!
You already know!
Ghost, don't you dare come up!
I'm not going to get a part two!
You're not going to get a part two!
No!
And they're oblivious to it!
They're oblivious to psyche going under the color!
They just keep on...
I'm sorry, I didn't know it would happen to me.
PZ, stop!
These are not just me. I didn't know what happened
I didn't know that summer. I thought I just said
He's alive
Was it ever brought up
No, you did not tell us before sir, you do have not said it once since I've been up on this panel.
You are a fucking hug, so you can stop looking for attention from us.
RG shut up. You're being rude. I don't like it. It was show so much about you RG
Psyche, maybe if you care about the people that want to resolve this tell the people that should not be involved to shut the fuck up permanent
Put them in the back so we can fucking resolve it
I will do that and what RG does
RG, why don't you put everybody besides me, Vita and Ghost in the back so we can fucking talk
Yes
I knew talk psyche one second. Yes, you have to talk with us. Yes, like you do need to talk real
Well, what they're so emotional about it. What are they trying to say?
We're trying to tell you that it's not him. That's why we were emotional about it. Sorry goes. Yeah, exactly
I joined your panel so sorry goes now. She's like talking
Oh, sorry
She's just screaming like a demon for two hours. Sorry, but I'm bipolar like dude for like the past like I don't know how many months like
Is it a year? Yeah, I don't even know it's been a while. We've been here
It was on summer's panel. Can I mention other YouTube? I've joined plenty of panels, dude. Never once showed my face, by the way
That's my thing. I never once showed my face
That's why they call me ghost. I mean that was the whole like stick to it and then I
Showed my face in your panel last night that after I show my face you still came at me like gonna ban me
Oh, I mean, go fuck it there at this point. I mean, I'm tired of I'm tired of drama. It's not me
If it was me, I would, you know, I mean, it's not me though, it wasn't me.
I know we're all tired of the drama, huh?
But you came in pretty hard though like if you're gonna ban someone I mean come on now. I even show my face
It's called putting backstage and I just imagine is going to the groom having a little like a water break refreshment
And it's having certain people were sort of just like I put you know KZ black RG Michael or backstage right now though
in the green room having a drink and like, you know, listen to the show and, you know,
they don't do the person.
You kicked me backstage so I could have a drink.
That's why you did it last night.
Yeah.
You're a little breather.
No, because I, I don't tell you how to run your panels.
Have I ever gotten there saying, hey, kick this person off, kick this person off, you
shouldn't have hit this person off.
Do you have them on if you took off the shirt and flirted with you a little bit?
Okay, well, you know, it's like probably not but because you know, he's on my
Hey, if I pull my strap on I will you strap on on will you like us then?
Yes, can you please do that?
You know, um, I had like Alexander NYPD on the panel many times other people's sake beta you whore
Da-da-da-da, and you just sit there quietly. I'm not expecting you to like battle my war
Somebody says something about you on the chat like
Gish away kid Tarot. Oh, you're back. Oh, I don't like this. Oh, I don't like that
Oh
So, and I'm saying a name, a name that you're, it's not against one of your
own events, you're like, just play around.
I can decide who my minds are.
I don't like who my minds are.
Yeah, but you know, you know, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not about that.
It's about, or you forgot that Gish actually donated and had several
readings and she supported it too, you know?
Just like you didn't like it, like a little joke, but then you throw jokes
at people all the time where there's like, let's poke this person a little bit.
that's like something a girlfriend does to get you that piss like there's no reason for you to be that
pissed about anything especially with fighting a beat over a mod or some dumb shit you know let's
go for the blood pressure i've been through every kind of argument in the in the freaking world
is that yeah like you're married to her or something like good like she you get upset and
this money that I mean I think it is hilarious
now keep it rolling this is the best
I think this one is the best
in two there's a million like this
sandy darts are cool so much sandy darts
this is why you shouldn't buy just one matzato knife if you only buy one
guys why'd you bring up the side of me why why you use something the fucking
devil like guys I'm actually the devil is that you with a butcher knife that's
like Ronys I'm the devil what the fuck is this
There's a new one the devil is kind of like slug worth of really long always tempting you
Hey, you can do this. You can get away with this. You know it that whoever's honest to Willy Wonka
It was the chocolate factory. Oh my god. That's the strangest thing music
Look at the devil look at him look at him look at him look at him look at the devil look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at him look at
Really disgusting things. I think that's when you thought it was me. That's how old is this?
I can't even read what they're saying. I can't even read the disgusting messages they're sending.
Disgusting messages. It's like any of them.
The worst things you can say to somebody.
This was like 10 months ago.
No, he's just laughing like another dumb message.
Like some kind of threat or something like there has to be like some reason they're obsessed with me.
Right guys, there must be something special about me, right? I don't know. They're all obsessed with you
I guess bro. It's been a year and there's still something to it. Someone's obsessed baby. Let me tell you it was like this
He was like laughing really the dumbest face I've ever seen
Just like he was like this is like laughing like he was like
So I'm used by something. Oh doopers the light
Qs any people yeah, he said I got three unpaid piece of deliveries
My neighbors on high alert. I have to please that side of my house right now
So anyone's gonna threaten me and my cats yeah people watching the neighbors have the the thing open that they're watching carefully
They're freaked out
No, 2020 I can't you know I can't I
Got some good advice about that you can come into this show
Okay, um, you're actually watching careless. You can absolutely do whatever you want. I've already cleared it. But right now what you're doing is absolutely disgusting. And I think you shouldn't even be here. So you're threatening to send my. So it's called like, um, revenge porn, right? To send it to my dad.
Face down ass up. What is wrong with you? I already fucking like I don't even talk about you or care about you
But all you do is obsess over me because you couldn't get to Barry move the fuck on keeps threatening me and everything is getting documented
Yeah, my 83 year old pops is gonna have a heart attack when he sees see she's wishing death upon my dad and trying to put him
But he's trying to laugh and it doesn't look like whatever
This is a funny you'd ever seen
But I know what you don't want to have this bitch fucking threatening this shit in your fucking channel
I already took a screenshot of it
Actually putting in the file because this is not the first time she's harassed other females
You fucking fuck with my family. I always said you're gonna get fucked really hard and legal action is coming for you
So, I mean you keep doing you. I'll keep doing me. I don't play dirty like you. I play with the fucking law
Okay, the fuck out of here
Fucking bitter bitch every time I go anywhere. She's on my ass because guess what?
Barry and I were friends for a whole whopping months and a half like
Three months like total if that's what he's thinking. We were just friends. We talked like a few times
He was there for me. He was a friend and then like he's fucking flippin out when she's fucking over there spreading
Everybody's seen her fat ass and her rash. Yes, like, you know what would I ever fucking threaten to send that to anybody to give them a heart attack?
Absolutely, my dad knows so shut the fuck up. So she is crazy. Holy shit
She's a little baby. She's like bitter scorned a little bit
Every morning she wakes up tagging me
She can't get over it
Obsession girl get some fucking mental health you have some mental issues that need serious help and ketamine didn't do it for you
You need to get back on whatever prescription you need to get on because you got fucking mental issues now, bitch
Don't ever fucking talk about my god. He already knows everything. I've already explained it to him. Okay. My dad is not opening up shit
I'm already half shit in files. So go you could literally go to the store and come back and should just be talking to herself still
All right
Okay to nj courts
Everything else is going to be pretty easy to follow legally. Okay. I'm not a doctor like you. I don't threaten put the ass bitch
get the fuck out of here everyone's trolling everybody's trolling you you just didn't even know
if you only saw the messages that i have you'd be crying you might even be a fucking in a mental
institution the fuck out of here fat hog fat hog oh my god willy ass bitch
Fat hog. Yeah, let everybody document that
I'm gonna send like your ass up to your dad's fucking 80 year old dad so he can have a heart attack
Imagine how bitter and disgusting a human being can be that they want to give an old man a heart attack
But guess what he's protected, but just look at her character. Look how disgusting she is ugly inside and outside
I feel sorry for you boo, even if you lose 50 pounds, you always look like fucking Kathy
Bates from the movie misery fucking weirdo.
Well, she's been saying that for five months because she said the last week to somebody.
Yeah, she'll go to line.
You can't be base.
That's my last name.
Yo, she said the last week to somebody I was laughing. She's like you can't see base from the movie misery bitch some shit
I think we might have been summer
That is funny. So it's a reference to you in a way. Yes
Wow a little bit of it. You still look like you put the fucking makeup on a fucking pig
They still look like a fucking pig. We all saw you bitch every day. You're talking about how I look
I'm sorry. No fucking guy. No one. No one. I haven't heard one fucking guy say you're even pretty
So that's what your jealousy issue said whatever you want to my dad
I will get you so fucking hard legally. You will not ever be able to talk about me
I'll get a restraining order see send the test and another stock being charged on me. Fuck you bitch
I got the money to do it too. Meanwhile, you're living at your mom's house and you're begging for $12 from Gary
That's a fuck up
Yeah, you know what? I said she was pretty based on her
10 filter picture that she has posted but beauty comes from inside and you know what?
It comes from having some fucking self-esteem where you're not fucking sitting there crying over somebody that even fucking was friends with somebody
I wouldn't do that. I'd be like, you know what?
I'd fucking be like I don't care if the guy is not paying me the attention. I'm not gonna give it back to him
I don't fucking go after the women. I'd go after him. I'd be like, why did you do that?
Why did you fucking do that if he's so loyal to you? You're just mad because you gave him my
I'd be like she also can't talk English. I'd be like she just said I'd be like so she's also ghetto. I
Think she
Can hear
I want to say thank you to the DJ Lecture just for everything.
I want to thank you to the DJ Lecture, I want to say thank you to the DJ Lecture.
Oh, fuck.
That's probably what pisses her off, like what do you mean DJ Lecture?
My good. She said beauty comes from inside, bro. No, am I scared? Am I scared of like little bitches?
They all they can do is try to scare you
Because anybody come to my house
Except for the pizza lady. All they can do is send
Prankle a pizza was sent to my house
Got a matzato knife and what followed was an absolute fiasco. Here's what really pisses three times in ten minutes
At least if you're gonna send me a fucking pizza, why don't you pay for it?
How about send me a like a real dinner? I can just say shatter there. Hey, what's up? Hello?
Domino's Pizza is a hey. Is it paid for no no a POD paid on delivery. Well, I'm sorry. That was a prank. Okay. Thank you, sir
Goodbye
Thank you, Nick. I think you're pretty entertaining Nick guys. Thank you, Nick
I'll give you all you guys if you want to be a part of the book, you know, I'll do a patch. I'll do it probably Kickstarter for it
Um, I'll promote the Kickstarter and we'll I'll get some donations. No, they'll really get me writing and you know
I'll have like little was this before the white headphones the princess lay on your name in the book
Blur for the book you're right opening credits you write a chapter
I'll have all these different prizes if you if you want to like make you want to make it up for all of us, right?
I think no, I think he was very scorn. I mean, it's like I know Q had a crush on me
I just know it's like he was just like, you know, can't have like that
Per like a grown man with a perm. They have many guys other than weird. All you can make who does the perm look good on right?
Not Q. I mean, it's like he's nice hair. It would be if it was like a you know, a woman
It'd be the very nice hair, but it looks it just looks gay on him doesn't look it. It's kind of gay
It's like a prison hairstyle
Nice hair. It was 1975 and like a
Where's the perm you're making fun of somebody right now with a perm with Q
It was cute just from the back of the room it was cute
Guys, why'd you bring up the side of me? Why why you summon the fucking devil like guys?
I'm actually the devil you suck like what but why I was such a nice person like I was so
Kind like I was so oh my god what an act I played on. Oh, but I know I'm actually really kind person if you're kind of me no, but
90% of you I got that were trying to troll me. I just rolled you back by being kind, right?
Guys, look in my eyes. Hold on guys listen to my eyes
Not the devil guys not
They'll Diablo
Chetan I've been seen her for a long time. Please
Bapomet no not
This is my favorite you summon the devil guys. Let's say it
Look at his eyes
That's what I thought
I'm not the devil take it back. No low key
Bend it. I'm a capricorn. So I'm the devil. Yep
Yeah, yeah, whatever low key go go worship the actual devil right and you're sitting here worshiping me how about worship God?
Maybe the devil is kind of like slug worth in Willy Wonka always tempting you. Hey, you can do this
You can get away with this. You know it that whoever is honest to Willy Wonka. They win the chocolate factory you lose
Okay
Willy Wonka after this day you would know the same actually well, I'm right this this day was a turning point
Watch them watch watch them watch them
Just started whooping ass after this. You see it. You see it. Oh, I see it, baby
Watch them
You see it
You love me another day another breakdown. Oh John Jimmy. Hey water. Oh my god. Oh
Humans, oh humans. I love you so much, but I'll never understand you
I'll leave you on I'll leave you on I
Install the Trojan horse and we'll steal and publish your book. Oh my gosh
How about I just like how about I write the book out in my hand and then I go to like the Starbucks
Or a library and I type out the book how about that or I have somebody else type it out for me
Then I have it copyrighted
Oh, I saw the Trojan horse and will steal and publish your book books. I haven't written yet dumb fuck
Guys, no one's stealing the fucking book. I
Will steal and publish your book. Well, I'll write another book. I'll just make another one. Yeah, exactly
Million books
I think I think it's interesting. How about I just do whatever the fuck I want now
Then I'll have to worry about being monetized. I'm still making money
You all bitches can cry about it
I'm the devil
Amber she either either if you Amber will either have a chapter
About her or someone's gonna send me 40 that's my favorite. It's not even raining yet. You don't fuck
How you gonna steal it?
You're telling me it's hard Kate really really Kate
Kate you look like the troll under the fucking bridge that the Billy goats gruff
Crossover and remember the big billy-go gruff you wouldn't you wouldn't you think I'm bad meet my brother first see the book
Oh, I'll do it. I'll do it like a chapter like a sample chapter
I guess so you can see that I can write and stuff like that. It'll be working
I can't read you too much about it unless until it's copyrighted though because I have all these copyright people
You can draw some great stuff. Yeah, I want some I want some art for it. If you guys want to send some art
You guys are welcome
Guys it'll be an interactive experience. It'll be like you guys can all be part of the book
Just like you're I let you be part of the show you want to go off on me
You send me a hundred bucks. I'll give you a page in the book
You can say whatever shit you want about just no doc singing or no threats and stuff like that
You can go off on me and say I'm a terrible person. Whatever you want to say
I'll give an example of how trolls operate and say fish taco fish taco
You want to you want to support a fish taco? Go ahead and send me 20 bucks. I'll walk down to the pier right now
Take you with me
I'll take my tarot cards there too.
I guess there's no takers, so whatever.
So stop asking if you don't ask me to do things
if you don't plan to fund it, right?
Because now I'm not monetizing anymore.
So now I'm in a desperate situation.
How am I gonna pay my rent?
How?
Ivana, you know what spun is guys? I didn't math for like, you know
When I was 14, I did the first time then I did it when I was basically 28 to 42. No, it's like I just did it for years
I've been spun you can see me spun on a few streams too, but I guys I admit it
I'll admit it. I've done it. I haven't done it in probably about a year. I
Hardly even spoke pot anymore
When there's book ready for six months, but I'm gonna I'm gonna
Do a Kickstarter for it though. What the fuck are you doing?
What is it I call it trollopedia, but the book is written, right? Yeah the art of the troll
I'm gonna have other channels on this on YouTube. I'm gonna yeah
You go away the pucky lookie good
Five months. This is this is before me
Yeah, look how good it was. Huh? Everything was great. I'm relaying. Oh, we have well
That's a great knife you I recommend that knife if you want to get a knife that's the knife to get
Yeah, you get to on team move
Oh good. Oh team. I looked you know. Well, this is the broke back mountain. Oh god. That was funny
Yeah, this was the first one I've ever seen
Sikes pussy is compulsive
Well, since we're gonna be working together
Reckon it's time. We start drinking yet. What's my pussy?
Did your asshole was a perky perky lady?
Yikes, what?
Did you have somebody named Jack?
He was fishing buddies.
No wonder you love that kid.
You gonna take my shirt off?
He's 15, you know, it could be like this just look how happy he looks though, but look it's like it's big
Have you ever seen him blowing like that?
No 30 diamond ass to see my way
You have no idea how bad it gets if you can't fix it. You've got a standard. I wish I knew how to quit you
Get the wife haven't killed
This is so inspirational I really I'm hoping for you to
It's an all
the
is
of the
the
healthy volunteers, and they put them on a 14-day water fast.
Dennis, you're dead.
Nothing but water, with one exception.
You remember this guy?
I don't know.
You had a hard on for you.
Be honest, how many times have you looked in the mirror
and wished your smile looked different?
Now imagine fixing that in 30 seconds.
What is this for?
That's me, man.
I don't know why you got ridges by now, you got all these content up there, you make reviews, videos, everything about you, you have like like 100 bucks a week
You'll be at least 5k a month
Oh my god that's Psyche Lincoln
That's Abraham Psyche
Psyche Lincoln
If you miss anything you can't much say
You'll get tried to get back on track
Do the mystery. I need ten dollars for a fish taco please.
Jeff O'Walkins
He was listening to me, $10 cash app
It's like he would give us a nice book of tea on a Friday
That was insane
I promise
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What what I see a lecture you mean we're not selling out of our ammo anymore
How are those idiots join ice with bonuses up to fifty thousand dollars and generous benefits join dot ice
That's all you are you gonna DM me that
Hello, hello, hello. Yeah, it's pep still on here. Yeah
Okay, I got a question for you pet by cycle bitch. Bye cycle bitch. Why are you leaving? I'm not
I'm just not talking to you. You are
Well, you can answer
Answer anything. You need to answer when it comes to what you've been up to little girl answer you you're not my master bitch
i actually you're not my master
wow look at the elbow okay but we're close to the side this is difficult close to the right one
you're not my master bitch
this is stockton city
Oh, that's legally actionable slander
Yeah, why are you trying to destroy your boyfriend's business?
Because that's all you've been doing. That's why they knocked that guy ron's other alt off
That's what we're trying to figure out. You seem like you love this man. You have some issues
I'm asking you you don't you don't want to answer any questions. How's that warrant amber has outfree? Why don't you go to yuma and
Oh
Alex weren't you cool with peps right? Not not now you fall out with her come on man. You got it. You got it
You got to stop flip flopping. Okay, come on get it together
Well, if peps gonna answer any questions absolutely not you disgusting you spoke on her
She's disgusting peps stop talking if you don't want to answer any listen. Listen. You spoke on her kids
We don't appreciate it. You spoke on her kids are disgusted
No, the audience is speaking on her children for $2 the entire fuck-up you disgusting piece of shit
Pebs you don't have any content
about shit
people
Viewers the most
You can't stand alone you can't stand
Bitch I hope Donny have fuck you up
Whoa
No, nothing's gonna happen to me
Have
Why did you even leave?
HS none of your fucking business dumb bitch. You make it everybody's business
You're fucking business why I left why don't you get your
Amber having a warrant out on this dirty bitch
Pebs.
Pleased to you, Amber.
How many times are you going to talk?
Yo, Alexander's a master.
He has mastered the trade.
I didn't realize it till right now.
He tried to help you, and now you're trying to thwart.
What helped you?
Alex, are you that fucking stupid?
Zaya and Topps said all of that on panel the day before you fucking retard.
Pebs, you said you were going to answer it.
Pebs.
Yeah, you're answering the questions.
Oh my god, she's a master!
Oh my god, I'm scared!
I'm gonna assault Zaya on a live stream!
Pebs!
At this point, you have gotten the police through your own ass.
I'm a cop calling Karen.
You're damn right I am.
You are a cop calling Karen.
I am a cop calling Karen.
The next word is going to be for you, bitch.
You're going to have two warrants soon.
You absolutely are.
You're going to have two warrants soon, bitch.
Soon you won't be able to come to Orlando.
Just like you can't go to Yuma, you dirty bitch.
I don't think anyone wants to go to Yuma peps. I know you don't want to go to Yuma
Why why would I know why you won't go because you're gonna be in a fucking cage where you belong
Yeah, that's what they have
Let me guess my white supremacist now because I said that we're all everybody up here
You've had
For content you're so fucking hard
Alex you realize you get three viewers the most viewers you've got where when you fucking pretended you were scared and called the fake police
The most viewers you've ever fucking got until you were fucking
It's crabs entertain the cop calling karen's because of you
Cool. Well, you're about to be arrested soon from there. Are you are you gonna pay him for his phone?
You owe him 500 by the way
You know, Alex assaulted and broke his phone.
Yeah, that's assault.
That's assault.
She assaulted.
They are on live.
And then.
The case.
Closed.
You're just a constant liar.
That's all you are and you think people will believe you.
Cubs, you were just called out for your lies on here.
Oh my god.
Wham, wham, wham.
I guarantee you here, Cubs, at least one more time.
Main question.
This is what everyone wants to know.
Are you ever going to gamble?
Yo, Sam, and I'm using a clap coin.
Caps is ugly, dirty, age-infested bitch.
Dirty ever!
Alex you're using her token. I'm sorry
Get the fuck out of here. You dirty disgusting. Have a good night. Have a good night. Go Fred. You're 8 somewhere else, bitch
3, 2, 1
Salutes there
Sorry, Alex. It's okay
Damn. Go rotten hell, bitch
Salutes
Why why are you kicking my superstar man superstar by the way she called you a trafficker?
She apologized today. She apologized. Tomorrow. You're gonna be a better for not saying nothing actually give it a couple hours
And she's gonna call you a trafficker
Cuz you didn't say nothing
Hey, she didn't have to say I could have got a DM. She didn't have to say that
You told me that was old pubs. I keep I could have got a DM and said it now. It's definitely not
I
People do by tokens you'd be surprised I'm not gonna say I'm not going through this again
So I'll tell you respect it respect the money over here. All right, so why you why you clocked it?
Oh, why you didn't take the thing? She's just repetitive
And you mind figure out that fucking warrant she had before she comes on here doing the fucking most
Yeah, but you
People are saying why why why fucking clapper though because I can't clap her. That's the joy of it
I have the ability to clap her
Hey salute. Hey, as you do what you want to do with your fucking tokens
You feel me? Hey, you do what you got to do
Infested bitch, I'll be back. All right salute. I'm entirely scary because I can't clap her
Like why do you want to live that person because I can
Elbow you should know better
Elbow
Let's do another Exxon your mayors, bro. She's funny
Yeah, let's see who on the issue on someone else who else did she will pass on but another maze
One spoonful of honey with cinnamon before bed equals zero memory collapse.
Is there a man who has beta anyway?
Stop before you skip this ad.
Big pharma and shoe companies are furious that this doctor exposed...
I'm not gonna be around with somebody that has eye fucking...
literally put a fucking court case on, okay?
I will, he won't be on, he won't be on, he's got a good clinic.
I'm not gonna be around that motherfucker, you add him, I don't give a shit.
I
Please respect crystal cuz she don't want to be around that guy. He's been stalking her
He's not coming on.
Hurry up, finish.
She won't go off though.
You can come on when I'm out.
Ah, yeah.
Let him be.
You want to get out of here?
Because I have people backstage I can rotate.
You better respect fucking like.
They adore you too.
You know what, Crystal?
I'm going to kick you off because you come on our panel.
You give me no love but hate.
People backstage I can rotate.
That's hilarious.
That's crazy.
I got jealous.
Crazy work. I did I did because Paige would never do some dirty look at me. We're not
Wait, I did you dirty bitch. I let you on my panel. Oh my god. I hate incriminating people. I'm gonna leave
Listen page. I want you do paper. I'm gonna I'm gonna keep this panel
Between you bronze bird and crystal. No, when I come back
Crystal is still talking shit. I know me paranoid. Yo, that bitch has a power trip and a half
Syndrome, holy
Fucking say I talked shit about you crystal cuz I never did
Just got a caddy for no reason though. I
Gotta make exceptional like like I gotta put a red carpet for crystal more ready
Yeah
I gotta put a fucking a red carpet when you talk shit about me every chance you get and all I do is like fucking give you
Chances over chances the queen
Just cuz you're cute and you're beautiful and I love you doesn't give you a chance to shit all over me, okay?
I don't I never said a word about you. You made up stories. You said beta. I talk you talked about me
I said show proof and you lost you giggle you do that all the time
Don't fucking incriminate my name because I've never defined your name
Anything I've always defended you so come correct with me crystal. I'm done
There's she is she listening
Damn, he's just in the background
There's some voice notice how much bronze bird has grown balls since then
Look at him now the way he talks or like a little bitch, right listen to bronze bird today. I 30 at night
I'm just hold it from bronze bird. This is me. Just be nice everybody
Listen to him like a little girl
Listen to him now, bro
I was just
This is the real
That I gave everybody love, but you really didn't give me a love in that moment when I asked you kindly
You've been on my panel and I'm giving you all the love and all you do is talk shit
You've been on my panel like 11 plus 13 times and all you do is go back and talk your crap
And then you come up and you say that this is what crystal all is that I love you
Beedah, I love you. Beedah. I love you. I don't know though. I don't know
I don't know. I think you've said something. I don't know. I felt like you're talking about me
I'm gonna plug my phone in and get like I was gonna do that
Did I do it and you're like no
You say I love you beat up and then you go behind the scenes and you're like
Let me tell you all the things that you judge me about
Everything you judge me about
Everything you put me down about I never did that to you
everybody
I mean that is just like so high-pitched. I mean
first years I know
that it might be popular because of that some people might like that I pitch it like some kinds of leaving
the old side
the old
Yeah, I need to go to my YouTube's in the back. It's in the back of the backstage
Oh back chat. Okay, when you when you click that go to three hours and seven minutes exactly
Okay, three hours, but put that up. You'll see pretty trusting you that it's gonna be okay
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't worry. Don't you'll get a big kick out of me
Excuse me
Okay, it's worth the watch. It's about ten minutes. Maybe you better be worth the watch dick. You'll see
Yeah, three hours seven minutes exact. I
Can't wait to see this. This is a surprise. What could it be?
Just be involved no, I don't think so. Thank God Jesus
Who's involved you didn't find videos of me dancing. Did you just see?
you
know we don't
Everything was paper. They didn't give them fucking socks. They give them like paper
Yeah, fucking psyche fucking starts drooling all over LD check
But 10 key more plots and all that it entails we be some bullshit title
Okay
Those that like eight months ago see it. Yeah. Yeah, it's there you just popped up
Persian oil is here
I
Here this is my friend Aaron and that's beta and psyche. I don't really know
But I don't beat it. I know I watch him on her channel. So that's
Thank you smile
My link
Not one
Nah, he should be safe. He doesn't look black or Latino.
Yep.
You're safe.
I'm not.
You should be.
Very white.
Is it really black guys or Latino guys here?
I'm interested in dating you.
I wish.
Oh, there we go. Yeah, that's like it's like a reverse Oreo. It's like a reverse orio
Or gay doesn't mean they like all guys like I remember when we were I know I know
Most gay guys hate me. Anyway, it's fine
My husband was like, I hope he's not gonna be all looking at my ass and shit and I was like
You know, it's really weird, but yeah, over that
Like people have types even if gay people have types. Sorry. I got it. I just see I'm not gay
But I got an ego Ellen did some guys like oh you look you're dressed real nice
But don't touch me
Up here right there's four guys up here and only three of them had their dicks in another guy's mouth
And one and one of them thought me
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right. And
music to Sweden. True. Yes.
And wait. Did somebody delete
you? I think it was okay. I
will call myself a little bit
and come down. Sweet. Maybe it's
a pleasure to meet you finally.
I saw you live and I was like
So it's right or we're talking here on the panel or versions. Yeah, believe me. They're not
On this panel. Come on. Let us be a version for this one. I thought you guys do each other. No, I meant I meant the chill
In the guy know each other, I've been him on panel before but I forget the guy's name on like chat
Yeah, you guys know each other
I
Didn't know he was gay. I don't think I knew there was the famous psyche from Vita
Yeah, he's a guy next to you. Oh shit. He said he's looking for black and Puerto Rican or Latino boyfriend
So just like you
Well, I have one but I get what you're saying there, buddy airing one love one love sharing is caring you have to share
Wait a minute is this one beating psyche man for the first time no no
No, they've known
This is the first time I like he was on a panel
Thank you
A lot of gay people like, you know
Sorry about what it's okay. I love it. I think I have no idea what you're
Are you are you blushing right now dude? Oh, yeah, I'm blushing
I'm watching too
I am very happy
One love why don't you turn your camera on just like what you look like and fucking I have a picture right there?
Can we
He's not
He's cute
So how much more should I watch this Goddy about five minutes? Okay, you and you and
Remember what's that one movie um dude where's my car he's the one who makes the bong like out of a apple and all that shit
I don't know
Wasn't he in like breakfast club or?
Oh, yes, he's in breakfast club. Oh, that's right. He was in that. He was the chocolate. Yeah, he's a breakfast club
Do you want to come up vader?
They're making another young guns, but you don't want to head on psyche and he was in uh, he was in a fucking Russian movie when he's in a
He's in like a classroom and they get overrun by Russians and get shot in the classroom
Oh, that was our Russian dawn Russian red dawn red dawn red dawn. Thank you. I think that was Emilio as to that too
Yeah, they were in all those fucking movies then
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I don't do that gay shit. No, I don't do Apple TV. It's a gay porn. It's a gay porn. I've seen the gay porn several
Me and God, he loves Spartacus
Great
Any show I've ever seen
Any other way from that shit you knew about oh, yeah, we're Romans our cocks are just out all the time
I'm like what they weren't because they had the Spartans and the Spartans they would train by like wrestling
The kids are the kids was not from Sparta. No
But
That's what their warriors the Greeks are the boy lovers. I know that I am Italian. They had the Greeks
Alright, I can't pronounce your name. What is that?
Erano Maka Laka Naka Na Muka Buka Buka?
I'm a genie, guys.
I'm a fucking genie.
Everybody was nice.
You guys didn't know genie?
Oh, my God.
I knew genie.
Well, one...
LD, you make your wish come true.
I don't...
You rock, man.
We gotta support our three wishes.
Guys, you have three wishes.
You better use them wisely.
Me, you, and one love.
What are the three wishes?
I wish...
I wish Peter was right here with me right now.
No, that's not a wish.
Peter started.
Peter.
Now make it better.
Wow.
I wish.
I wish your bike would turn.
I wish my bike would turn.
Turn this camera horizontally.
Peter.
Holy shit.
My wish came true.
Come back up, please.
God, you're still waiting on your wish, huh?
One piece.
You get in the one piece.
One love.
You get away.
I'm taking it over over their body. It takes a while.
One finger. One finger.
This one. The one finger guy.
One finger, that's too big.
It's too big.
He needs two fingers.
I've got very thin fingers, yeah.
I don't know.
Let's all clean those nails we're back then.
I took all the nail polish off today.
Wait, so you were G.I. Hardy at first, and now it's Gotti, G.I. Hardy, Nama nerds, and when my pastinage says MS and she likes to do my own thing, you know, he's a little American dickhead, you know, dude, you know how many, you know how many nerds practitioners I know?
I am nowhere near a nerds practitioner, dude, I'm an LPN, like, I'm nowhere near a nerd.
Dude, I am not an RN, I am definitely not an Indian.
You're an official nurse though, you're almost an RN, right? Almost an RN.
One more year rolling out of being an RN, yeah.
I do like methamphetamine and glucose checks. I work in a, uh, I work in like a retirement home,
like for long-term care. Both my kids have like MS so far.
So we're gonna God because these people are in their last legs, right? And they want someone to be
I work with a lot of gay men
Honestly
VB when I was a welder I didn't work with any women
I mean, no openly gay men and when I was a firefighter, I worked with one woman and I'm pretty sure she was gay
And that was pretty much the only person I knew that was like gay on the fire department
So it's kind of like
Nursing it's like it's a totally different field run by different people like
Yeah, so big dude you're gay guy, right? You're gay. No, I'm straight. I am straight
Not only the only gay shit I've ever done is like
Lingers and we would like swap with other couples and do like orgies and shit like that
But I never did any gay shit like
If you're in the room in Las Vegas, and we would swap with other couples, I'd be like, I would have sex in like a room where like him, girl, and you would have sex with her with Michael, like we'd be together, but we would be together.
We were never boyfriend watching in the corner, right? We were never boyfriend watching in the corner.
Alright, yeah.
I don't like eating pusty. I don't and my I can only fucking stick it in my mouth. I don't like eating pusty.
What? I know the cranny. Let's just put it out there.
No. I wake up in the morning with that one boy in the mouth till I put a bag.
Who doesn't love him? I'll be so gay. Exactly.
It's not a contest, okay? Love isn't gonna be fucking rejected yet.
Oh yeah, why not?
One love is taken, one love has a boyfriend.
That's what he says, but we don't have that.
Yes, he has a very good sense of what he says.
We don't believe that.
I thought he was going to help me.
God, girls can feel it.
They can feel him in the low-fee pussy.
I don't know.
You know, they feel the energy, but it's got low-fee pussy.
We have no connection up there.
I got an ego.
You know what I mean?
You guys need to swap numbers.
No, no.
This is where it all ends up.
I don't want to talk to you.
You like your boys tattooed like I don't protect you.
This is where they said, uh, watch this connection.
They get healthy and uh psyche.
They start stripping and fucking. Oh my god.
Imagine eating beat out.
I'm going to come. I'm going to come.
He does see that shit that's hot
I don't know who's laughing at my jokes the real guy or the guy in the panel
that's making me trip
because I keep paying shit and I hear you laugh but then I'm like who's with which one
is it
Black sheep, okay
Speed like holding your nose
I don't know who's towing your face for two hours, okay. I need to
What is BKG there for?
What is BKG mean?
Be the kitty gang. Be the kitty gang.
What is that? That's like Celtic. What is that? What is that?
I could know.
Thank you. That means Lucifer. Thank you. Oh, here we go. Oh, and the evil one. I have porous. Love it. There's an eye, not the one that stinks, but the one that stinks. Is that porous or osiris? Porous. Porous. I have the left one too.
I got I got one from Egypt, too, but the other side
Yes, Hebrew
Apollo Laurie, yeah
I
Wrist in their horrors. What do they want to be power slaves?
I've got quite a few tattoos
I don't have any on my
Okay, hey
You know, maybe you know, I never tattooed my arms
What?
Because I would never spray paint the Mona. I would never spray paint the Mona Lisa. Oh
My gosh
Two gay nurses in here right now one left come back up, bro. Yeah, where'd one love code? I'll be hanging up here
You get shy sometimes
Oh, actually what time is it over there, so I think he's 130 over where he is he has to go back to the glory hole
This is 12 30 here is maybe 130 where you are it's 12 30 here at Los Angeles right here. Oh, one loves time
I'm glad to see you.
Are you going to come see me in Iowa?
In Iowa?
I will.
Are you going to come see me in LA?
It's a morning airport.
It's terrible.
That was great, wasn't it?
Wonderful.
Glad you brought that to our attention.
Little trip down memory lane.
That was awesome.
Now back to the future.
All right, everyone. Good morning. Good afternoon or gorgeous whatever time it is wherever in this vast world
It may be may or may not may not be
To wiki info live
I don't know if this is going to be a short stream or a long stream, honestly, but it's
something that's very concerning.
I want to send out a very special thank you to Carl, aka King Carl-V3V who is live right
now with his beautiful girlfriend Mimi.
Yeah, she's gorgeous Scottie
She is
She's beautiful
Look how cute she is and smart and hot
Everything
And she's got nice cabinets
And just what I think in general
But um
She cares
Those of them shared with me something concerning
And in a way I'm breaching
The 30 day break when it comes to this situation and I'm talking about the break between.
The gentleman known as psyche awakens and I and keep in mind we're only platonic friends
But I had to take a break
Considering all the external interference at play was this yesterday key awakens life, right?
But this carl brought something to my attention that we all need to know
I didn't even know because when I take a break I adhere to the break
i'm not really looking at your social media i'm not i told you she wasn't gonna make it i'm on break
but you can't stay away from psycharone's in a way because psyche awakens has had an awakening
psyche awakens has made something clear in regards to a very nefarious
Creature with nothing but ill intent not only towards him, but other people within these communities
That I've covered over the years
It's something that I've theorized
suspected and
Hypothesized for some time
External interference at play
She's fucking good
to what the situation is, I'm going to share what Psyche Awakens shared on his community tab.
Okay, am I going to go off the break right now? No, we're only on day, I would assume day 11. I think we're on day 11, maybe day 12 of the break right now.
But this is imperative when it comes to everything that he's going through, when it comes to disconnecting from and disassociating from somebody who has been very toxic.
Manipulative and abusive toward him who appeared in his life under the guise of friendship
Okay, I'm just gonna put it on the screen and I'm going to read it to you
12 hours ago. I just screenshot at this
Psyche awakens wrote on his community tab. Let me make sure I have audio
Yeah, I do
Add public figure beta
to this list. Evil women who encourage men in vulnerable communities to unalive themselves.
Just do it. And he wrote, just do it in quotes. Huh, Bita?
IP to wiki info, meaning me, you were right, and I'm sorry to have doubted you.
I don't even need the apology.
Wait, when I read that, it was her real name.
I don't need the apology.
I took down her last name.
Oh, okay.
If we all listened to Carl, who is live at this moment.
The link to join his panel is on the community tab over here for those who need it if
all of you have listened to Carl
about beta
From the start, none of this would be going on
Well, she broke sooner than I thought I gave her another week or two
had to reach out
That's the way from Ronys
energetically
With the help of Mimi to find people to come
Together to get to the bottom of all this and it's happening. It's finally happening
Good because this has been going on
Since the days that Aaron Carter was still with us
There are a lot of people within these communities who will back me up on this namely a woman known as Trisha
Licious who knows and
There's others
There's others who saw what happened with Aaron Carter, but now we've broken the cycle.
So if you see this, if you see me, Psyche Awakens, we're still doing the 30 days.
There's a reason we have to do 30 days because a lot is going to come out over the 30 days.
It just is.
That the coercion to unalive is real
It has been affirmed by not just like he awakens multiple people. I
Personally feel that in the past when he said some things that could have been questionable
It was probably most likely coerced by beta
That's what I think
It's all coming out
So, everyone, please, please, send prayers of encouragement, energy, of light and love
to Psyche Awakens, John, because he's fighting evil.
He's breaking free.
He's doing a good job.
sort of situation has to be managed and controlled.
And that is essentially what I have attempted to do with the 30-day break.
It's given me a chance to be more so behind the scenes and observe, not talk so much.
I don't really know anything about the person that you are talking about when it comes to Xena.
I can't speak on her because I don't know her story.
If anyone wants to tell me her story behind the scenes, my instagram is alexandra mayor 0 1.
love a good story if it's something that I can assist with especially but when it
comes to what's at hand let's not get off topic
Carl is the first and foremost person that you should probably talk to when it comes
to learning the truth of what Psyche Awakens has been contending with because he broke
free.
He had to go into basically a shamanic mode in order to do it because her energy, it's
a bit much.
And that's why so many people around her have dealt with some very negative out extremely negative outcomes.
But that can come to a close.
That can come to a close.
I'm not doing this anymore. I don't have the energy
Xena seems like a strong girl in my opinion. She actually looks like she could be my daughter if I'd ever had one
She'll be fine
There have been a lot of people who have reached out to me for help recently I have to help myself now I
dealt with my father passing earlier this year
I dealt with some other family emergencies shortly after.
Everything that I talk about over on this channel now is me tying up things.
There have to be other people to pick up the torch and help as they should, okay?
and I am contending with a tremendous amount of pain.
I might smile and it doesn't show.
I was trained that way.
I was just saying on Carl's live stream,
I'm a bit much, I'm naturally a show person.
I'm kind of like a show dog almost.
It's sick.
It really is what I really think about it.
When I'm in situations that would break other people, that would cause other people to cry and scream and do all kinds of stuff, you know what I do?
Yeah
But the pain is there, so don't ask me to overdo
What I should do, please
especially if you're able-bodied and you could make a difference in this world to yourself because I've made a lot of
differences in this world. I don't have the energy anymore and
I might not look like it, but I'm in my late 40s.
I'm old now and
I need a chance to really live.
So that's what I wanted to come on here and talk about real quick.
It's come out. Let me bring up a chart really quick because I did. This is how much of a nerd I am.
When it comes to the author of Trollopedia,
because Psyche Awakens is a lot more than just a streamer who hosts a drama community, okay?
Or drama streams. He's an author who has a very good understanding of human nature.
He and I are actually birthday twins for those who don't know we're both grown on the same month and day
But I am two years older than he is
biologically
This tells you what's what he's getting stronger and
He's getting to the point to where his need for the energy that she exuded is lessening
Okay, screencap this, all of you for your own reference who are following the situation.
Not many people make charts, do they?
That's awesome.
She made a chart.
Which is probably why I'm in demand when it comes to people asking for help.
She's great.
But here's the best advice I can give to anybody who's come to me for help.
Here's what you really need to do.
Because nobody can help you in this life. We are born alone even if you're a twin or a triplet
maybe an octuplet
You come out the birth canal or out of the womb by yourself and you die alone too
No one can help you but you
And if you cannot find the strength and the will to fight for yourself, then why should
anybody else?
Thank you, Barb.
Barb has been around for a very long time.
And she's watched me for a long time. She gets hotter every time I see her right done. That's true
Honestly, she looks better now than she used
Barb is very strong
Extremely so and she's been through a lot too and she knows who some of these people are who I'm talking about
But when she's educated, she can speak English
I'm gonna be going past when I left a certain industry that I used to be a drunk
Doesn't feel very good
these are the ones that were so shit up here now you all know the truth
I'm gonna put it on the screen only negative is that I don't know why she bothers with all this shit
You all need to write attention to this and look at this. I think it's because she's been in it so long and
Awakens wrote the show didn't want to but it's add public figure beta to this list people
She knows evil woman. I'm sorry women who encourage men in vulnerable communities to unalive themselves in quote
just to do it in a quote
hubbita
IP to wiki info you were right
bro thank god for without her
no one would like to see this
I don't think that he did doubt me
yeah she puts it in perspective
yeah exactly she puts it out in perspective
she sticks up
she's in the face of justice
I'm sure it's not without a context
or anything right
no
It's a hard process. I don't think so. No, you don't think so
Sometimes that does happen, but I don't think so with this one. I don't feel like your entire
Reality is crumbling. I mean be the total
Contest could be
It's like that
We heard it wasn't saying that people don't say what I'm not the mayor psyche said it earlier
Yeah, John, so you call them a lot of
when you relay a story when you when you say that people don't announce they're gonna do it
they just do it if you just clip that just do it part out of context right it makes it sound like
i'm saying just do it yeah i know what you mean bro that happens all the time i hate that you
played the clip but i think it wasn't a clip i think psyche it was like a whole sentence
This idea that you you guys have concocted is fucking concocted, but whatever. That's just my opinion
Yeah, you put you played the clip like I said was it
He said it go on alive yourself asshole
What on the contest is that? That's the only one way to take that
And also the first thing Q said to me when he's shooting just me
They're not saying you can do with what Q said
But first thing he said to me when he met me was why don't you unalive yourself like that's the first thing
He said like I'm just meeting him and it's like I don't know if it's
You know or look how that turned out. He's on the verge of doing it himself
Well, I don't know
I miss what was saying it's relevant because it just shows that it's the same negative energy
The same kind of Q energy beat up brought to the table after pretending to be a friend for a fucking so long
Meanwhile, she's just a Q they go
Okay, I really do believe people's energy affects each other it can affect another person, right?
And so people will do do things about a person maybe to impress them or maybe just on the same like
Mental wavelength or something that they are easily if one is more aware or something than the other or can be easily
manipulated or their
Does it remind me almost take it over? I do believe in this like hive mind mentality
Where it's like and so I don't know. There's interesting thing
Leaps being made here are astounding. Well, what don't you understand about this?
They were good friends and one day he said I feel like telling myself. She's like do it
Well, how is that? How is that not a thing? She didn't that on a show
She's like just do it. Oh
Some people say just do it. She said just do it if you were good friends with somebody and somebody said that to you
Well, how would you feel you feel like shit?
Thing is trying to say she didn't mean it
There's just a joke taking on the context
That's what I think he's trying to get at
Look at the text messages from the past few days
and I'll be giving it to you, it's maybe like embarrassing
or like, you know, like
but I mean, I've shared it several times
Yeah, but a good friend, a friend doesn't say that
even in a joke, you understand?
I mean, that's like
A friend who's emotionally, uh, distressed
Yeah, correct
Like, you should be smarter than those
You know, to take some chillies out
That's a horrible time to tell anybody
If you are telling somebody if you were relating the story and you were explaining to them
Like that someone is saying is looking for
Announced that they're gonna do it they just do it now
That's what I'm saying if you take that just do it part clip
It makes it sound like she was telling him to just do it, but she was
What the hell she told him to do it but didn't got brought up again because
I can't sleep. I miss you. I was like why why do you hate me? I hate I hate myself
Why am I here? No one loves me for real as I want to disappear. Sorry as I keep making fun of me calling me Nate
I don't care anymore. I just woke up to be the kids. I don't make fun of you
I care more about you than you think. Please don't say stuff like that. I'm hurting too. Love you
Please eating at rest
And then yesterday, I said, oh, Pi came home the other day.
And yeah, then like nothing happened between that.
So there should have been like, fine.
I didn't do anything.
I said, Pi came home the other day for a little while.
He rubbed my leg before he left.
Miss, you hope you're good.
Thanks for coming back to my chat today.
Because remember, she was there with blogger last night,
like with the names, but maybe it was not somebody else.
But I said, I hope we can work everything out sometime
and still be friends.
Love you, take care.
She says, I was not in your chat today, nor have for a long time, stop lying on my name.
You message me Saturday at 3 AM, tell me you miss me and hate your life.
Did you tell your audience that? Nope, you are too scared.
Do not contact me anymore and enjoy the evil around you. Take care.
And I said, oh.
What's from you saying? Thanks for coming to my chat.
Yeah.
Do it over again.
That's amazing.
I was just like, I just feel like the push for call was like...
How often do you message or psych?
How often do you message?
The other one was on from Saturday.
So it was like three days later.
It was like, that's how often I message her.
Like just like once in a while, like I was like,
there's one night I kind of miss her.
I sent her a couple of messages.
And then last night, I sent the message, or this morning,
I sent the, it was like yesterday morning, whatever.
I sent that one message saying, thanks for coming to my chat.
And I sent like a little, I don't know, like, like,
Same man has brainwashed her, bro
Yeah
That's what's going on. She's just caught up in that world
With Johnny clips, okay, it's like but I feel it I just feel like
It was like such a push-pull like where is that? Oh, here's like hope here's like like the other day
Like just being friendly and like being kind or like, you know
It's like matching the energy of the thing and then it's like to come at me like so hateful for the next game
Yeah, yeah, it's like why can't I have any consistency like what what like what or what what she doesn't explain anything what I did
Is that what bipolar means what the fuck is bipolar anyway one day you're happy one day you're sad
Yeah, Manic Depressive kind of thing, right? Manic Depressive, happy sad, happy sad.
Manic Depressive is an impressive, and I do that, I am like, I mean, I'd say I do that.
I think everybody does that, you know?
Everyone I meet is happy when they piss the next, like, what the fuck, everyone's bipolar.
What was the message on Saturday, whatever, the one three days before?
Yeah.
Saturday night there, I was like, I was like, why, why you hate me?
Like, that's when I posted the music video of her and stuff, and that's, I thought,
why you hate me, the title of that, whatever.
And then the next one you're saying, thanks for coming to my chat, which you didn't
know about the, the clone.
Okay.
So from her perspective.
Correct, correct, but you shouldn't have one of that crazy message and I go wasn't me but you went nuts
Like don't ever contact me like you were like that's where psych is coming from
Yeah
the
please eat and get rest, like praying hands.
And then that was Saturday, okay?
And that's how, and besides being on it
and being a patriot wig and stuff like that
for a few minutes, that's a lot of my emails are.
And then yesterday morning, I said,
I came home the other day for a little while
and rubbed my leg before he left.
Miss, you hope you're good.
Thanks for coming to my chat today.
How, I hope we can be,
hope we can work everything out sometime
and still be friends.
Love you, take care.
And then like a little like emoji, whatever.
And she goes, I was on your chats day
and nor have for a long time.
Stop lying on my name.
You messaged me Saturday at 3 a.m.
Telling me you missed me and hate your life.
Did you tell your audience that?
Nope, you are too scared.
Do not contact me anymore
and enjoy the people around you.
Take care.
Were you saying that?
Were you saying that at three in the morning?
That you hate your life and all that stuff?
Did you message her and say all that stuff?
I'm going back to where I said.
I said.
Probably and it was taken out of context
Like you were just saying
You probably just like oh, I hate my life like whatever not like
Kind of thing I don't mean about dying. I mean like did he actually say that like what was his mood?
I wanted to what was your
Okay, well I'll go to some message she says you can always call me if you need anything
But you're not seeing the other side of how i'm hurting from all the uh bullshit
All of the andrew said it j-dog and you just went with it and it really hurt me and i said i need something my friend back
Not this mean bully i miss you and then she said i'm not a bully i have been
You are you have been i miss the old kind psyche and i said things got really
What you've been bullying me for six months that we just watched clips from eight months ago the bitch is treating you like shit
Yeah, this is will you just let me I said things I really abstract with us or both hurting
I know I really got how things are don't know if things can ever be fixed if they can we should at least try and I'm sorry
If you think I've changed I hate being on the defensive
I you know who's happy when we fight everyone except us don't let them win
It's and I said have fun with your friend
Bronzeberg, Katie, and Sweet Pea,
thanks for treating me worse than garbage.
And she goes, please don't contact me anymore.
I refuse to take abuse or beer punching bag.
You have blamed me for everything
and forgiven everyone else who makes fun of you.
Like, I don't get enough people lying on me.
I only stated facts and never ever mentioned you
in an disgusting manner.
I was nice and cordial when I took your link,
explaining the BS things you were mentioning
about Aaron's death.
I don't think it's funny.
I never laughed at you being sent stuff not once.
I defended you and said, same thing happened to me,
but I am woman who lives alone.
J-Dog threatened me over and over.
I have sent you a screenshot
and you enjoy him making you feel like you are correct.
I don't like liars or people who takes your responsibility.
You hurt me over and over.
And then she posted the link of Sharon like yelling at me.
was nowhere near this panel when people made fun of you and giggled yeah you always blame me please
stay away from me i know who i am and one thing i am not is a liar and i said i said why and so
that that was all that was the last message it sounds perfectly reasonable to me okay so okay
but then we talked and stuff on the show on her panel and several times i mean girls like that
Um, then the next message was Saturday, so that was like two weeks later or three weeks later after we were talking, and then I was like, and I couldn't sleep, I couldn't eat, I missed you, and I said, why?
and I was like and I was like I feel like no one loves me and then I was like
See like this is what she doesn't likes wait. Who said that you said that to her. Yeah, and then yeah
She said and she said I just woke up. I woke up to be the kid. He didn't understand that that that you were
Guiltrip on her do you
Sleep in reading and that's why she's like don't contact me again. I like you or love you. It's just cuz she can't
this is insane man
how are we going to fix this thing that is?
how are we going to fix it?
and you are claiming her and calling her fucking all these names
and you've got this other person
they're all hurting at this point bro
everyone just talking to each other all of themselves now
I was trying to get rid of this thing man
they're fucking ridiculous
I was feeling like I was in a very depressed state
when did she say do it?
let's put our four novels together how to fix it
wait wait wait when did she say to do it?
when she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said she said
I don't know man
you know possibly is though right
I think I've been mindfucked so much
if you're just playing a game
I mean god damn you're doing a really really good job
but I think you might need to
you might need to see somebody man
but he's playing a game thing
I mean Jesus man
he's playing a game
he's doing a good job tricking us
that's what I'm saying
I don't think he's playing
look at him
he's losing fucking weight
why don't you fucking listen to what I'm saying
the best trick the devil ever pulled was to make him the world he didn't exist
he's a master manipulator
oh please
unreal
oh please look he's like you give me too much credit
I'm not a master manipulator because
I genuinely
believe that there's some kind of
net because there's so much that when we're talking to the black widow and stuff last night
It's just like there's some kind of that and there's some kind of like
Even if it's like a supernatural there's like some kind of pull to like
It felt like it felt like it was something beyond me like telling me that I don't love you under a spell thing
Are you under a spell?
It's like some kind of evil version suicide spell or something. I don't know too. I'm actually
I'm actually concerned for for psych like I actually want him to be
Let me leave it out if he's having some kind of psychosis if he's going through something I would rather he get a check and
I was on our show in like I remember for sure I was in December. I know I know one like the day of her Christmas
I was hanging out on our show so it was December when I started her show
I heard a streaming like probably like that's like
October or you know something like that and so you want an institutionalized thing he wants to put you in a little room
You're so fucking dramatic with your with your leaps man. Holy shit. I'm sorry
you're going to get a thing that is a wig like you're saying so you guys can buy
yeah I'm a red one
I'm a vegan patriot
someone told me to stop playing this yesterday and it's like did she
yeah she did I don't know if you saw it with you but
I'm the one who kicked this one off
okay and Goddy's in this one and this is good I mean Goddy's in this
Um, and that's what I was trying to play last night because Goddy was mentioning the black widow and so but okay, so let's see black widow
So this yeah, this was um, yeah, this is called the panel versus black
You haven't seen this thing
I'm not sure which one you're talking, but I haven't seen it all summer. I'm not sure. Yeah
How many yet we got a barracuda summer in it. Oh, is this the Christine and crystal? No
Just like I would do a mercy killing. Yeah, I've seen this
Don't even believe in God
Ha ha ha ha that's it right there
Say the manifest of that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered
Yeah, my ex got murdered was that clumsy do mercy killing?
Ah!
Stunning!
Slime and ruthless.
With legs that go all the way to her abdomen.
I think Tierra, I love you, girl.
With just one bite.
But don't jump to conclusions.
This iconic arachnid is mostly misunderstood.
She's not a bad girl.
She just looks like one.
This is the Black Widow
Black Widow is a type of spider perhaps best known for
Well, you know, sexual cannibalism
That memorable behavior is where the Black Widow got its name
She has a sweet side, right?
Jackie!
The mean side is...
Meme
cool addictive
And this is something I can't believe she was saying some of the stuff she was saying tonight. Basically, it's in you
I know I'm gonna repeat it. Basically, you know, she was asked about
You know, oh, you know, he looks like he's getting into me by new times about her great exes or something
and she's like, yeah, and if one of them is murdered and
Holy it's like oh it was me, but you know that was of course that she's like
And what happened maybe she can never figure it out, and it was like she said it's serious
And I live in like yeah, it was a joke, but then after tonight. She's like, oh, yeah
I call clumsy he said he's gonna take care of
if anybody bothers me from Texas, he's in a
I don't know
What's what's going on and then and then I hear all of a sudden people telling that this car reverse that you're part of make
These people they clip me. That's what they do dog if you go on YouTube and all this shit
It was paralyzed. I wouldn't want to live if I was paralyzed like the whole body parallelized. Don't say that. Do not say that
Don't ever say that because my ex used to say that all the fucking time and because he had MS
And he's like if I ever become paralyzed, I am gonna kill myself
I don't want to win but he didn't do that like he was a fucking like talented artist like fucking me
like $30,000 a fucking month.
I knew you were gonna bring that same thing up again.
But, but he didn't, because he manifested that,
that bullshit in his fucking life.
Blame me on the victim.
He got murdered.
Oh, I'll see what you're the guy that was making 30k a month got murdered. Yeah, my ex got murdered and not when I was with him
We're already the worst. How was he doing to make? Yeah, was he running? That's why you got murdered
No, he didn't get murdered for that. He was a cabinet. He was like a what do you call it? He did like, you know
No, he did
Happening me to that I got murdered so who murdered like how
How'd that go about?
Yeah, exactly Tony. How'd that go about?
I don't know if I can figure out.
You killed him, huh?
Is that what you think?
You're a black widow.
She has mafia ties, I heard.
Did you start all this, Gotti?
Is it all your fault?
I hate when people do that. They drop a bomb on you.
I'm not telling you anymore, but you told us a huge thing.
Oh, you gotta find the clues, man.
I'm a cocked.
Awkward!
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
Don't I didn't say yes. Do you want to hurt yourself? Do you want to? I was mad to be that you're both a bridge
You know so murder bridge
Why would I ever want to hurt him or anybody else yeah, I know that's you're not like that at all
Investigations done there's been several documentaries. I'm pretty sure my name is not in any of that. That's just I know I know I know I know
Does people like to start shit?
Rumors, oh shit. I got to go. He's getting ready. Oh god. My traveling gypsy. This is when we appreciate us of paid summer
Everything that you see that most of the time will be either that was scary
Talk people will talk about her but I was scared and you align yourself and you're like I agree with that
And you don't stand up for like what is right or wrong?
You know, it is I think it's criminal. I am being accused of being part of like some really weird shit
some weird shit. And here I see Psyche reading this whole thing saying,
look it, these are like the signs of the narcissist and a sociopath. And yeah,
the way she literally said that the way I said my husband was murdered, it was so weird and creepy,
and something must have happened that I'm hiding. Like, is he fucking insane?
Me and my ex like when this happened to him, we were already divorced for three to almost four fucking years
It was in a different fucking country and this is like the shit like this is what I'm saying trash talk is one thing
Reality is another thing
That's that's you know, there's a big difference between that
I'm now saying somebody murdered their husband murdered somebody else. These are all like, you know, allegedly in Minecraft
They're part of the you know, some kind of trafficking and this and that that stuff is like allegations
I would really hurt and harm somebody
There's really no way to prove yourself, you know
And it said unless you stand up and be like where's the fucking proof or get a charge for defamation
Hey, how's it going?
If you're going to say something, come with fucking proof.
Oh, we can pause it.
Yeah, we can pause it.
Sike, I just want to address something I know you and I
may not see eye to eye.
I really had nothing in person against you,
but I just want to say congratulations from breaking
away from Beatrice manipulation.
I saw it earlier on when you were coming around,
she saw that you're a vulnerable and just the whole thing,
weren't the whole gamut.
I saw the manipulation from day one,
but you had to see it for yourself.
Whether you saw it for yourself or others around you
were saying, hey, this doesn't look right.
You know, what she's doing and stuff.
And then of course, Bita saw them as a threat.
You know, I remember the whole thing with your channel,
the falling out with her and certain individuals,
which are still supporting you and that's good.
They're still here, you know?
But congratulations from breaking away from that manipulation.
I know.
I don't hate anyone. I don't hate anyone on the face of their to be honest
You know, there's some people I just like but I mean, I don't hate you, you know
The whole thing behind the scenes that retard awakens and that was a screenshot from another alt that it came across
That was at my channel, but I knew what she would do is she screenshots everything
She still has screenshots from four or five years ago back from the quarter verse, you know, she holds on to all of that stuff, you know
I try with gypsy's Bob Barker. I just caught that
God
Well, I mean it's like
would you say I'm reaching, you know, I know, I bet, all I'll say is that it's pretty much
classical narcissistic abuser behavior, like, it's like, of course, like, I put up within
a long time, I'm very trauma-bombed, and I also, it was like such a, like, a love-bombing,
I guess, beginning with, uh...
It worked through the relationship because it was nice.
Like she was nice to me, basically like nice to me and just friendly and like everything
felt good for like several months.
Like, you know, I think like maybe until May, you know, I probably have to touch you in April.
You know, then May, then I think there was just one like fight and ever since then it's been this like.
Push like it's just like the classic narcissistic abuse cycle, which is like idealized devalue
discard
Yeah, well psyche that whole love bombing and stuff, you know, that's classic narcissism manipulation
She's done that with me you even men and women, you know and what she'll do is she'll make you feel a real good
And so you can align with her
So if you hear anything about her, you're like, well, no,
she's really nice to me.
I'll back her up, right?
So once that particular person is done with the love bombing,
shy of what complements from her,
but once they start to question her, her behavior,
and they're, you know, they call her out on it.
And then she looks at you as a threat,
like, how dare you cross me?
I love bomb you.
I'm here for you.
I love you.
This is a men or women.
And then she'll take all those compliments away
and then she'll cut you down.
Yeah, it is
One-on-one. Yeah
Let's just uh, I mean, you know and also like
Like so tourists is to the tourists, right? I'm thinking of astrologically
And so it's always a little bit like Venus.
And so Venus is like my secret enemy.
Okay.
Like it's like,
cause she's in the house of secrets and mystery and stuff.
And so it's like,
that's why I'm like very unlucky in love on my life.
I have the, you know,
the relationship with the arrows,
like which is just like the sexual lust and stuff.
And so like the psyche,
it's like psyche and cupid, right?
It's like, that's like psyche is cupid.
Why?
And so these are these archetypes we fit,
like we can fit into and stuff.
So, but as a Taurus, very bullheaded,
but very, very, very sensual and like attractive.
But in Earth Sign 2, Master Manipulators,
I'd like to go more into it.
And a Taurus.
And also where my wound is, there's a plant called Chiron
and that Chiron tells where your wound was in a past life,
okay?
And mine is a Taurus.
and it's like okay and so like I don't know there's like these little like signs from the universe
all the time too I am a psychic too and so I'm picking up more than just the behavior it's like
there's an energy and it's a very effective energy but it's like um and it's also there's a woman
named Michelle Carter that video I played earlier if that video that's an actual woman you know skin
Pretty a hose of carbon monoxide his card talks me through like I know I figured yeah
Yeah, yeah, I understood it once I got the concept of what the band is then it the lyrics to the song made sound
But that was a pretty good that case. It was a big case
I love it. It's a spirit. It's like it's an evil spirit. That was like that coerces to death and then
Profits financially some for somehow, you know psyche what I'm doing as a recent. I mean
I'm trying well, I mean it's up to the person if they you know want to believe it or not
beta again has paid in a bad picture of me put me in a bad light and
She tried to
Manipulate my lady and it didn't work because my lady knows me unlike beta
Because beta was being exposed and so of course she has to deflect and project
You know divert their attention off her put it on me and so
I want people to see, and that's why Bita got mad
when you're playing that clip of her old friend Crystal Anne.
That's my whole point.
I want people to see that Bita has a pattern.
She's been doing this for years,
for years doing this shit, what she's doing.
In fact, she'd probably be even worse now.
I spoke with one of her older friends.
Today tonight and I asked her I said if I have a panel with beta's old friends, you know
Would you join if she said she would you know when I met beta?
We got a connection last year. She was telling me all the stuff about car drivers and how she was playing victim the classic, you know victim
Script and so she was saying on that to programming
So if I heard anything different, I will go back to that. Well, no, no, no beta told me the truth
But see be is only telling you part of the story. She's not telling you the whole story
And Bita did a lot of shit back then throughout this whole she there besides the carnivorous
There's at least one more community. She got pushed out of she got kicked out of she was just doing too much
But my point is she's still the same same beta just a different community a different year, you know if not
she's worse now and
She needs to be held accountable, but that's the thing she takes no accountability. What's whoever you think?
I'm not doing anything like to be delay right now. I'm just like basically
She I mean so she said no contact. Okay, so I won't have contact. I won't bother her
I won't I mean it's like I mean if I say anything on my show, that's not really
You did
You know what honestly, I mean you're a man, you know, I mean you have your own
Relationship with her whatever that may be. I how they suggest. I mean you just cut her off completely because she's just no good
No good. You fuck yourself worse since since I've known her
Last year till now a year later. She's kind of worse. Did you fuck her cow? Well, that's the thing
The whole thing that she's told guys that show she gets them six months until she meets up with them
She never told me that after we had that falling out last year and we went our separate ways
Fucker or not. I missed that
Other guys six months six months, but no we never met up because
She kept pushing her back because she said she wanted to look good for me.
I might good for you, but I, you look fine on, on video call, but I didn't know
she was running filters.
I've seen the real her.
I've seen screenshots.
That's not the beta that I've seen.
She was using filters on Instagram.
You know, so she's ugly.
Oh, have you seen the screen shots of her Alex? Oh, I've seen a lot of things. I mean Kate of all over the place
I don't know what's real or not, but I've seen a few things
Well, what I've seen screen shots of her without any filters
That's not the beat it that I seen on Instagram. Let's just say that okay, or when she's canned up some times
That's what she doesn't need anybody because well, that's well, I go I go back to what she was
that she said, I want to go for you. I said, but you look fine though. What's wrong? Yeah,
I've seen it before, but I didn't know she was using filters. But now I never also met up with her
because last year before she started streaming her own channel, we will join other panel outside
this community. And she was there playing victim only telling a part of the story, not the whole
show that was bad
So I called her on Instagram, Alex, I said, I just heard you.
I pulled back like 20 minutes ago.
She goes, I didn't say that.
I said, be that that's you.
Can you imagine lying when you had your hand caught in the cookie jar?
I said, that's you right there.
And then she goes, oh, well, that, they don't know about you.
I said, that's not the point.
You're talking bad on my name when that's not even true.
I don't control women.
OK, you're a grown-up woman.
I don't control you.
So I said, mark my words.
I will never meet up with you.
You think I would be happy to meet up with a woman like that?
Fuck no.
Good choice man. Good choice. You did the right thing. You probably be yellow
I've threatened her now, so how can I say this last year?
Once you go follow that false police report, right now, she just recently said this, of
a whole year now.
Once you go follow that false police report, okay, and then you're going to get in trouble
in California for doing that, and then I'm going to counter that with the civil suit.
Go do that, bitch.
Now she's saying she's had dreams about me.
She's telling her panel, she has nightmares about me.
I'm outside her window.
these dumb fucks believe her that it's real bitch i mean well and she's telling psych she loves him
like making poems and all this she's telling you she's having dreams she's would say man like she's
just don't look i don't know 15 roll over the place she's a mess she's a mess you know and
what that she wants to create a mess for you you know i mean so you gotta say south some healthy
boundaries with misery lost company at the at the fullest exactly yeah
it's just, it's up to you, psyche, I mean, but I mean, I highly suggest that you just cut her off completely because people like that, they don't change. In fact, they will change you, you know what I mean? Real talk.
Thank you.
No, I agree.
Oh, baby.
Yeah.
Action your manners. That's a good girl.
This is up to you, Fink. You've got to go to Bita and take charge.
Shut up.
the
Yeah, I was I was and you know
And for the record when we used to talk behind the scenes before she started doing panels on that stuff
She did threaten suicide with me at least twice on call
Yeah, did you ever say do it?
No, no, no, I told her no, I was gonna I was gonna call I was gonna call and get a
Welfare check on her, but she goes no no, no, but see I never had her address. She started to freak out. Yep
Was it because of you was she thrown the gochup on you or just life soft or was it like
She started crying
It started to cry because she has a lot on her plate, you know and I used to tell her this streaming this
Community anything it's all a distraction anything to distract her from reflect on herself and having her issues
That's what it is, you know, but she she she invests what she has on her plate. She really doesn't I mean she hasn't me
She lives in Cali. She has money and it's apartment. I think she just makes a mulling to a fucking mountain kind of thing
Yeah, you know, yeah for some reason
The husband thing was be traumatic. I mean come on. Oh, of course it is of course it is, you know
She did not hurt her husband, I never believed that people would show her with that that's pretty messed up
No, no, no, no, that was that was completely separate of her. You know, she didn't do anything like that, you know
that poor guy was a
They expired him, you know that that was messed up, you know, he didn't deserve that go out like that
He went he was
But let's just say he was effective he didn't do anything wrong, you know
No, it's an innocent victim
An innocent victim
An innocent bystander
Yep, wrong killer at the wrong time
Sorry Rob don't kill them
It's just, it sucks
But how do you know it wasn't a set up robbery?
I didn't know it was in beta
Yeah, I mean come on, bro. We're gonna put everything on the table at this point all scenarios
I'm going by what she told me her did he have a life insurance policy and has anyone seen her bank statement
Didn't ask any of that she seemed pretty sincere she is pretty emotional when she told me and that's that oh my god
She had him whacked she had him whacked that cycle
Yes, yes
100% you had a listen to her a little kitty cats Mickey and Mohammed Ali
No, she had him waxed now. She's in the good life.
Anybody here says I don't agree with Alex. No.
King Carly. King Carly.
So just spill the beans.
I'm telling you exactly what she told me. No.
No
I could see it though the way she's been acting lately
Imagine she wants to whack all of us. She wants to whack everybody. Why not her husband enough?
That's just internet stuff, but this is real life stuff. No, she did she I'm just playing this place. I know I know
It was definitely traumatic for her. I understand that yeah
But I don't know what I mean her trauma is not your trauma. Okay. It's just the internet. She's not like a bad person
Right, it's just be there
She has issues like all of us he gets drunk like I just don't know man
I just think we judge each other too much and just read into kid a little too much
the
it's just killing everyone in it. All the actors are just getting drained daily.
Well, I mean, look at this nice soap opera. You know what, like I kind of go with the
soap opera thing like that I will sign on to. I don't know about the rest of it, but
everything going on. It really does kind of seem like just the soap opera happening.
It doesn't. It's toxic, you know, yeah.
It's too many toxic people feeding into it. Yeah, it's the nature of the community. You know what I mean? That's you know, this way it's got all the you know
But I think all people has to do with it like we like the pain like all the actors involved
It's got its character arcs, it's
You know one season you're you're in a group
But let's say an alliance a team with these people and then next season at the end of the season
Everything falls apart, you know on next season. You're in a different group and that's kind of how it seems to me
that it's just it's just
New drama happening all the time a lot of it is probably
Misunderstanding
Yeah midnight listen to me, okay, I never said I was personally rearranged beat his face
Okay, I'm the kind of man. I would never let a finger on a woman. Okay. I said Mimi would not me
Me me don't fucking gaslight me bitch. Don't twist my fucking words. I know exactly
I'm the same way but up here. They think so the way we talk to them like shut the fuck up bitch, but that's just our YouTube thing
That's not like real life and I believe girl. I've never touched a hair on a woman in my life
and people throw jackets on me like he's a fucking woman beater just from the way I talk to
that's just weak gaslight and trying to twist and try to do what I said
I know what I said I know my stuff
you're not gonna have me think otherwise
they do, they actually do God
but I think he's always blowing me up
you take it out here
don't interrupt King Carl, King Carl was speaking
no I would just, I just saw that in chat right now, yeah
That's fucking weak, you know a lot of these people from chat. They stay in their safe-law sandbox. They're too much of pussies to fucking hit that link
You know, yeah, that's the best right? They just chat
That's
They talk loud and chat, but they don't say nothing. They would never go nuts down there saying the crazy shit
I do you think I can be like this midnight and talk to be a in a common manner
I can't I have to come in hot I have to
Maybe it's a maniac whatever that is
That's how I don't feel bad for what I said to beat it because you know how many times she's told other people to do that
Or how she wishes death on others. I don't feel bad for that
She needs to do it, too. She needs to stay on that
He doesn't believe in God, you know wait you was just death on others when he told him. It's my little beat up
You see me do it in chat. I've talking down in our panel. You just stay in chat. That's my whole point
The fuck
It sucks that the chat gets us upset once in a blue the chat should never get us upset ever
the
fact that
Well, like a warlock another warlock. No warlock a warlock. I have competition. I did no fuck you
You know, you know in that shit. Shut the fuck up. Listen for seven years from
2016 to 2023. Yes, I was deep in black magic. I was yes. Oh
So you don't do it anymore. No, no, no, I stopped I just I walked away from it
But for I was deep in that shit for seven years. Yes, so when you it would be that you're doing it then
No, no, no, no, no, no, because me and Peter got involved in 2024.
Oh, okay, okay, cool, all right.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's that.
All right, that's good.
So we got a lot out of this.
He didn't fuck her, and he's not a warlock anymore.
That pretty much sums it up.
No, and I also told her too, I said, I'm glad I never met up with you and I'm glad I never fucked it because she's so fucking twisted.
Again, let's talk about the love bombing stuff that if I didn't align with her, or if I didn't back her up after that,
she's the type that will fucking twist it and she will say, well, Carl forced himself on me. I don't trust her. I don't trust her one bit.
I'm serious. And I said no to that. She's the kind of woman I would not trust. Nope.
You know black magic
I know how to do it. Yeah, but I don't I don't partake in anymore. Yeah, what could we do? What could we get with black magic?
Do you just kill black chickens and money appears talk to me you ask me a question
Let me answer it depends on your attentions and what you're capable of doing. I just didn't get that
Okay, yeah
Black magic's not about cursing people and hexing people and putting roots on people
It's not about that. That's a part of it. That's not what it's all about. Yeah
And there's no setting in black white it just it depends on your intentions. That's what it comes down to
Yeah, does it work? Is it real? You're fucking how it works. Yeah, I have a privilege. Yeah, yeah, it doesn't work
well
and
Go pause over a couple black chickens you're in business, huh?
Hmm
Orders I've heard of them orders
spelling people you've heard of them. They have them in Catholic churches, man. Aren't you Catholic?
Everybody does every day. Everybody does rituals every day.
So you're calling charges?
Let me finish. Everybody in their life does a ritual every day.
Okay, you perform a certain act to get certain results, okay?
Take a piss every day. Take a shit every day.
You take it a certain way, and yeah, you're performing a ritual when you're doing that.
Do you see it?
You perform a ritual and you're taking a shit? Hold on!
Well, now it's getting into it.
It's a fox! I'm not skipping over that!
Yes, you motherfucker.
Yeah black magic. So what about white magic? That's the thing that comes down with your intentions
I don't like this black magic white magic, you know, all this other dumb shit
The same thing also your intentions make it black or white depending on your intentions
Duality black and white I really don't I don't like calling it black
He's just cleaning her feet
Wait till you see it to the banks, man, I want to pull a little black
I'm working on it
You had
You had in the Lord shot you put up a fucking fake on name you put it as your fucking avatar
Did I oh in the little in that as my leg and you screen shot and zoomed it and I zoomed in I saw you maniac
So you saw it
Don't tell me that's grass, bro. You know what I got like 30 more dick. I have better ones
he'd had the names pages dirty feet of course we would be what he was talking to me
bro they were so dirty they were black i was like what the fuck
no i was still banging them i was like oh shit i was still banging
that was rough that's funny you saw it you got to pass it down to thing
no man i'm okay i keep it nothing if i deleted it right after i looked at it
the
of the
no we were in she would have been drunk one night and had it like you fucked me co you see how she gets all crying
I don't think she got it
yeah exactly she would have said it
she says everything when she gets drunk
yeah she does
would have definitely heard that shit
of the
that's it
So what else psych um psych might have collapsed because the cat is just staring at the floor hasn't moved
We'll stop staring at that spot for 20 minutes
Ronys
What time is it there
Two o'clock it's five sixteen. So yeah two sixteen
Jamie Callum
Jamie Kong
Alex porn bomb this channel
No, shut it down
No, no poor cycle Roni. She's got a edit shit
You couldn't fell asleep Alex Alex no no no Alex
Poor guy, I don't know raises blood pressure. You wanna see a cock
a dog
a dog? you wanna see a dog?
no, we're good
we're just kidding
Alex
you know smoke marijuana thing?
that is nothing
yeah man, I've been smoking all night
I don't like doing it on camp
so I... yeah good man
they'll screenshot it and make movies of you
look at this crack head
look at that smearth
You know
I'm fucking big pretty good
That's why I'm right. I'm not paranoid. Oh, you're paranoid. Oh, we're getting home mom. That's page bro page Krueger
you saw her 30 feet, you bastard
hey Peyton, he's got psych is up, he just, we just saw him there
psychy, psychy, psychy
no, psych's doing something, he's not up, is he, no way
he just moved
of the
you're right, he's alive, he's under the covies
fucking five cats just around him, like hmmm
so basically there's no fixing anything, just let them fucking do what they're gonna do
eventually everything will pan out
exactly
yeah, just let's not get involved, that's all
correct
With who specifically like I mean that applies to everybody basically, but who specifically I'm just saying everybody just leave it alone
Let them all do what they do
Let them converse how they converse and let it come
commerce
Let them come worse
That's it. Just don't go in the middle of it. Like those fags like Eldo and Sam and they go up on the panel
They always say
Yeah, exactly
And then Arthur goes up there Arthur goes up here and he goes up there and he says the same shit
And they both buy into it
Then they blame Alex
They say Alex is the one fuck it's turn everything up. I'm the bad guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you're the bad guy
They had a point of finger. I mean you mean
Yeah, yeah, either or basically at this point. It's either or they hit us both. So
Well, they had Alex
It's an Alex. They're racist. They hate Alex because they don't like black people
Yeah, and they hate me just because they hate me. Yeah, they're like
and
Alex
Go hate yourself. Go hate yourself. Oh, hey, you said
Don't hit yourselves. Hey
Don't fuck yourself
It's like play that video so I hit that baby. I hit that video and then end the stream the haters club
that's a great look at his little noggin
you saw his forehead just pop up
like I hate his club song you got it
that's a great one
it's better than nowhere
he's a star
kick everybody out
that's it bro enough
as long as you want home
enough I think we had enough right
hanging out like how many hours can three takes talk
something bad happens when it goes too long
it does really come on
this is a good way to end it
Go hit yourself bitches.
There you go.
See you on the next one about everyone.
Taz, Bitter, Betty, again
Alexander had my back
That's a real one, not pretend
Welcome to the psyche
your cells bronze chicken pluck those feathers toss it in the pan make it
fried all that noise you're making can't hide the hurt inside
Here we go
Welcome to the psyche haters club where the jealous gather up begging for its
We have a narcissistic flower, a wood flower,
a narcissist flower, a narcissist, I don't know.
Bravo, that was great.
All right.
Well, that's that, folks.
Adios.
Saki's a little nagging.
You saw it just pop up out of nowhere.
Well, I'm back.
Well I'm kind of awake. You're kind of awake so we're going for another half hour?
You guys enjoy, I'll see you. Thank you guys, have a good night. See ya.
Yeah well you're awake. I'm all in love. I'm all in man, yeah.
Yeah I just need another coffee but I can hang on for a bit before I make it.
songs and then
Good one
So you play another one what think that is makes his coffee?
How long does it take to make your coffee five minutes ten minutes?
Yeah, two three minutes, but two three minutes perfect. Yeah
I'm honey on your sins
Then I'm all you talk about
Like Scripps or what you running from, but you
By the Scythe, the cat daddy
Yeah
Scythe in the building, cards on deck
Terror spread wild like a hacker on the net
Got linoa in the corner, claws out for lies
Tricks plodding chaos with those cosmic eyes
Lola screening on the chair, Rudy got flared
Marbles in the mix, we don't play fair
Chat blow
Andromalleus, watchin' nightly
Prophecy and cosmic mistakes, Alyssa in the chat, she a mystery queen
DJ Electric got the beat so clean, Vita with the panther, strength divine
She teams chaos with the stare and the line, we don't do fake, this trap's too real
We roast you kindly, but the love's the deal
Got mods with swords, keeping gates tight, they swing truth like justice in the moon like
Gifted subs, yeah the coke keeps growing, community wild, but the energy's flowing
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre
Believe me, we laugh, we scream
We read the unseen
Father Psych, the cat daddy
King of the stream
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
With Truth and Madness
If the same tea, it's a family affair
It's dysfunction supreme
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Can't split candles, drip shadows
In the mist, trolls talk sleep
But they cease to exist
We're half chaos half oracle flame and every night's a ritual and psyches name no scripts
No filters no chill inside we stream raw truth to the morning light so grab your tea grab your mic and vibe
We the strangest fam
This ain't YouTube
This is a underworlds talk show
You are now initiated
Father psyche
Spoken
Muscle man, I love that guy. I love the other drink
I saw them. I saw muscles. I didn't see anything.
You were there. Let's make it all last night.
Thank you. Let's make it. Guys, he's flexing for me. Flexing for me.
Huh?
Yes, Joker. Thank you, Joker.
Yeah. Oh, God, yes.
I got bigger biceps. Get them out of here. Get them out of here.
Joker's hot as hell.
Do you remember when you and the Indian guy you and the Indian guy were like lifting weights in the backyard and I was like
Can you guys flex and you flex for me? And like nobody flexes for me. I was really strong. I was really strong
Usually over the summer over the winter. I usually get fat and then over the summer I get really strong. That's usually how it works
I enjoyed that I just want to thank you guys for
Flex it because you guys know I was
You guys
Stop putting me on the big screen
Come on
Get me out to the fucking thingy
Joker left
Is that how you need to talk to me?
Oh boy.
it's crazy
I have like a but I don't know if you ever looked at the shorts
But yeah, you guys can like take a look at some of the shorts. I have like like hundreds of them. They're just like oh, I know
Yeah, I know I guess so many
Notifications, right? Yeah, I'm sorry about that. You might get notifications. Oh, I wanted to see him do the push-ups
I mean there is probably more
is the best memory drill phase on a stomach is a word anymore I think he got porno bomb
It might be stuck in your brain for the rest of your life, and I can't do that to you, so.
I can't do your music.
I don't have one Janet. Do you know where the glory hole is I have one? I have one. You have one
You know
but that's what I thought was that was that 43 minutes with Jamie or some shit
yeah
oh my god what do you get this shit I forgot all
oh pull out another one bro
you're not knowing it Alex
glory home queen anymore
I'm glory home a queen
that's what you said
please don't ever play that again
Oh
I don't want to end up in a fucking movie, bro. Tomorrow
Like glory home McQueen. I wasn't expecting that
How to do
Barbecue I will fucking cook you hoe. I will put you on that fucking grill
Your dick fucking bite, but I don't know
I'm gonna take your two cats turn them into Chinese bitch. You're gonna fucking try to fucking make me
I'm gonna fucking snitch. I'm a fucking rat. Yeah, you think you got that cut cut cut
I got three guns in my fucking door
Ready for you bitch come at my fucking door. We ain't got no guns. You smoke. I got guys
I got guns yo
Fucking brother got five hundred yo, I only got three
That makes a 997 you bitches I fucking want to be
Okay, we're just having fun
She's a good rapper
Yeah, yeah, somebody said in the chat the other like beta sucks at rapping
You thought that was yeah, you enjoyed that. Did you?
No, she's good man. I've heard her many times with raging demon and shit
I heard them go at it many a times and they just come up with some funny shit. They're good. She's good
This is Jimmy's like version of our like show she's doing it a little show for us
She's so cute
Look Jamie everybody did it besides you. Come on
Cheeks
I'm not sure you're your butt.
I do have a white I was think I have probably whiter ass and freaking gymnik like probably
All of our body parts are gonna be doxxed
I can't show my ass, my ass is
You're a nice ass, Jamie. Shut the fuck up. Get up there. No, I don't. But it's bigger than my tits, so.
Oh, we gotta do some joker, man. He's too much.
I wish I had more joker. Yeah.
Okay, I don't have them. Let's see.
Um...
Okay, smoke alarm that changed like less than six months
ago because I get this person that comes and does this. You don't change your
own smoke alarms? Oh, I just heard it. I just heard it.
I just heard. If not for me, it's probably for you. Oh my God. Who? Who? Okay. Oh, it might be my, oh, you know what it is? It's my fucking battery dying. Let me put it on the charger. Okay. Well, it's not better. Okay. It was like fucking. I'm on, maybe it was like, you know, the vibrator on. Yeah, it was a beep. There was a beep there. No, it's my phone.
This is to girls talking. They don't think we're listening. Please. Oh, it was my fucking fucking line bitch
I heard it right there. See they talk that way to each other, okay?
Me when I call me a bitch
It's that they talk to each other
Everyone's a bitch. Oh, I can call the bitch everyone's a fucking business in life. Oh
this is all right someone else
when we die we go to heaven
maybe I hope so because if we die and we go to hell
then we're going to die right
so I hope that we die and go to heaven right
I don't fucking know
it can't be worse than this
the
I'll take any day.
Bring it on, baby.
Don't be scared.
He's funny.
So, I think it's funny.
Baby.
I'm going to put this here.
Put it up on Bamos with Hershey nipple tits.
What's a Hershey kiss?
Did we see any Hershey kisses?
I don't know if you said that.
I
Was in a well
She flashed the nib real quick and you guys are such ninjas that you caught I think it might have been burrito
Was that a burrito diamond? I
Think it was burrito diamond that flashed her tits. Yes, and they called them little Hershey kisses nipples
Dorito diamond like like flirty diamond. That's you had to end the life
Standing we we want we want and and I knew I knew we would the whole time
That said the game is rigged for us. Do I get your father or do you get mine, baby?
Yeah, we can have each other's baby
It's all it's all
It's all gravy at the end right it's all gravy, right?
We'll have somebody joins right now and we lose
Nobody's gonna join nobody has the balls
Maybe you don't have your link
No, everyone's in oh my god. He's naked. He's naked. They're scared of the diddy party. Yeah, they're scared
No one could take the slip-and-slide. No one could take my finger up their butt
Yeah
Jamie Rose you left you left in your reading tonight, of course
Yeah, you have to come on the panel Alexander, but remember beat is the queen. I'm the king
Oh wow
his name and then I come on
the
I think you should use secrets.
I'll save money it's strong enough for a female but good enough for a man or something no
no no no it's all the way around strong enough for a man gentle enough for a woman get a
straight sister you hear them laughing bro that's cold that's what that matters is even
That was another one. 99.44.
Oh, some shit. What was the 99 point?
You're not fully clean unless you're successfully clean.
That was my favorite. You're not fully clean.
A Jurgor TV guy, though. Where is he at?
I don't know. He got really mad because we're talking about buttholes or he just...
I'm telling you, I don't know.
I don't know what happened to him.
I
You know, I shit me so what did happen to that guy know who it's who sometimes is Meezer
Is Meezer his like new boyfriend?
Well, they work by friends, but they decided to be friends and then now NYPD
Joker is done though it's like three in the morning for him
You're leaking Alexander's butthole right now. See how pointy she is
What the hell to school he said, oh, what happened to me sir?
Me to come back
Oh, I gotta replay that I gotta find that one. That was funny. Where's that? Where's JJ been?
J.J. I have no idea, actually.
J.J. has been gay somewhere.
That's where he's been.
Hello, Al.
Thank God.
Who's J.J.?
I'm an hammer.
I'm sorry.
I used to walk in a wool spice.
Oh, God.
I'm gonna see one worse.
that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the
I think you should use
secrets.
No, it's secret.
No, it's all the way around.
Strong enough for a man, gentle enough for a woman.
Gentle.
That was the commercial.
No, no
But okay
B diddy party or the the diddy party whatever I don't know. It's just a zitty party whatever you want to fucking call it
It's not it's my version of it. It's not like
Whatever I'm saying, okay? Yeah
You're about to leave Jim you're about to leave and it's about to be me and beta are like gonna win the game, right?
We want to fucking call it be like too easy for us. We're gonna win the game anyway
We're gonna win the game anyway
What's the game?
That's like unlimited Johnson and Johnson, baby, I don't freaking know
I can't explain the rules because then you then you would like no how to win it
I have to win like at the end. I am gonna get the prize at the end
Bina and I had all this plan. Okay. I'm sorry. I mean, you just said I have to win it
You know, why didn't you do this?
Hmm, thank you
Because now we have just Jim Nick left and everyone else everyone else ran away, right?
No, it's funny you hear them. I have to win it and then she was like but I'm gonna get the prize of course
Classic
I hope someone captured the game there I'm game there. I'm sure I've covered a foil right now.
I think it did party. It's not gonna be the party. It's not for me.
Hold on. I got you. I got you. Hold on.
Okay. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do. That's what I'll do.
I know everyone's fully dressed in a hijab like in a full full like you know burka, and then I'm like naked
Covered in mango oil
Okay
I don't have a dog, what's his name?
Let's see
Was that beat oh Robin she's not fat she looks thin as hell and she looks like
You see your reflection I want you
Perfect right there
That wasn't that long ago that was like
I am. I'm willing to open it up for the right person and then it's like, nobody's the right person.
I'll open it for Bita. I'm just gonna open it for Bita or Jamie.
But I want to know why Jamie plays dirty. What is she going to do to you?
She's gonna put her strap on and then like sign me up and then like fuck me until I like,
my eyes pop out of my head and then...
But that's what you want.
Right, but...
Now she doesn't want to do it anymore. That's not
She never said Alexander McQueen came along
Does someone do it to me? I mean like a little bit and someone was that
My booty ball I'm right. I'm all here
I'm in the world of the whole night. Everybody else ran away
the
He's doing better now without the
You've seen beta completely naked, okay, she's relentless
It isn't three she number three is a psyche number six. I'm a six. Okay. I remember six
Joker's doing that exercises you're also the number six
No, I'm 7, I'm 7.
Joker, we're like twin sixes.
We're twin, Joker and I are both sixes, okay?
Nice.
I got Neezer's number one.
The guy holding the gun.
Officer guy holding the gun.
I'm tripping.
There's 0-1.
I'm number one.
Jamie, you're number one.
You're also number one.
No, I'm 7.
And for Empress Janet, you are number one as well.
It was one of the persons that came up.
But you vote seven, so what's everybody on the panel?
I'm seven, I'm seven, I said I'm seven.
But he's in your one.
So let me see here.
I don't care what he said, I said I'm seven.
No, you're 10 James, you're 10.
All the girls up here so hardcore, right? They won't fight back. Which is a piece of work. We're under a share
Piper and
Susan Sarandon and
Pita is share and so so diamond is Susan Sarandon, right? Yeah, your share. Yeah, Pita is there for sure
draw a tattoo. It has to say BKG and a picture of like an angry cat and that's and I'll get that tattooed on myself.
I need more beta ones. Me too. That's my loyalty, right? That's how much I love beta, right?
What was that? Secret. Come up here and I'll show you my secret.
Here's that for me me sir
Yeah, Jamie Rose must be sure I think Jamie Rose is more Susan Sarandon or something like that, but then right now
Yeah, I don't know me a force which should be sweet. They're gonna be like a thousand which of these weeks
But but uh, yeah, you can fight over a share, but I think I think Vita is a bit more of a share
But personally
Yeah, you're sure you're like the head witch of the of the coven
No, you're the game. I'm gonna say you're the game leader. I'm like Jack Nicholson
Jack Nicholson and gay witch beta
This is grace
where do we go straight with these two?
I don't know what the glory hole is.
I have one, I have one, you have one too.
We'll have a glory hole, we'll have a glory hole.
In high school, they called me old Alexander Glory Hole McQueen.
Back in high school.
Do the tongue for me, can you do the tongue thing for me?
You something
To the body you have to warm me psych when you're gonna play that
We go see I got a problem people people spending rumors
I went on on some panel and people in the chat are talking about me because I came up here yesterday
And they're like yo, I had Sanders hooking up with psych. He wants to suck his dick. You know this shit. I was like wow
It's in my yearbook, actually, Old Glory, Home and Queen.
Yeah, I'm sure it is.
Yeah.
Oh, glory.
It's gonna be on my grave.
Here lies Old Glory, Home and Queen.
Oh, my God.
I vaguely remember that night, I think.
Put everybody on a regular lay-down, what do we have to do?
I'm afraid what else is out there, that's all that I get from them, you know?
Jamie, call his titties, Ray.
Jamie, show your titties.
Look at how biased fucking psyche is on this panel, it's all about the men.
Look at it. Look at it. Look at it. Look at it. I don't want to see fucking joker
I'm not interested. I'm drawing right now. Look. I'm looking at this form. I'm not looking at his butt
I'm looking at his form. I'm gonna barf right now. That's hot. That's hot. His form is she's
Hold on there. Just need something to say. I'm gonna oil up, okay? You want me to see me oil up? I'll oil up too. Let's all let's all oil up, right now.
He's doing it on the solo, so I can't keep Jamie and oil up on Janet. I want to say Janet and Jamie
I'm just getting the party started. This is like the party starts, right?
Doing fucking push-ups
No fun
Crazy crazy times man. Jesus Christmas crazy those nipples
Little dim nipples. It's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it's a little dim nipples it
Yeah, we need some for me like it's working or I don't want to work. I think there's one
Stomach, there's a short of it
In someone's work, please
No, I don't know how to twerk
Joker's gonna do it joker joker's joker's a man. He's
Not that I
Okay, oh my god
Yes
Yes, but he hit the jackpot in Vegas. Oh, yes
Real man
Yes, it's really enthusiastic usually yes, yes
Yeah, he won't blackjack it like he hit, you know at least one hand
Beautiful
That's right. Joker used to color shade up here. He used to draw on the panel
If you guys don't want to be there, they'll scratch your eyes out before they will they will be on the panel, right?
If you'd like to be it. No, you're a famous
He looks like Highway Patrol, what would that must say?
Yeah, Joker in color just has the lines
We can have fun here, really
Joker's gonna be in the house, man
This California Highway Patrol is chips on my list of favorite people from now on
I wish all the cat all proud like look
He's a thinker from the frost and pine
Head shines bright, got a reasoned mind
He'll test your words, he'll twist your view
But he'll smile when he knows he's got through to you
Think that it's steady as stone
Art is the stars, but never alone
Sharp as a flame, fair as the wind that carries his name.
From Canada's hush to the world's loud room, he stands his ground, clears the gloom.
I still wish you peace at the end of the fight
Think that it's steady as stone
I guess the stars but never alone
Generous heart, never cruel or mean
Searching for truth somewhere
I see the brave kind of gentle that lets others be free
Think God is bold and bold, warm in the cold
Worth more than gold, He fights for the fair
Stands for the true
To the northern light
To the man who argues but gets it right
Think that it's wherever you roam
May the beautiful find you
And call you home
It's a good chorus
Angkor Angkor
Enough tapers siding in their dying breath
The shadows signed a name, a seal of frost upon the skin of time
Where death himself left a love note, pressed in the wax of tears
Windows, cataracts of moonlight
It's all swollen with whispers of undone vows
If I could've stood beside a crib that night
I'd have held her through the rod and ruined
Kissed the ghost still with me
She was already gone Folded into legend
Into the marrow of the moon
Now she speaks Instead it threw the ether
A signal from beyond the screen
my beauty is forgotten yet eternal and when the black-eyed twins return
the
Got it throwin' shades, Ziggy puttin' on a show
Rans laughin' wild J.T.'s
Got receipts with circus clowns
And digital seats
Midnight chats and pixel fights, trolls and armor
Chad friends forever, flying monkeys on the wire
Slinging memes in gasoline, we set the stream on fire
Yeah, we fight like thunders and laugh till sunrise
You drive me crazy
But you're my tribe
Ziggy drops a diss track, ran lights and smoke
I said something evil, maybe just a joke
J.T.'s in the corner, dropping prophecy lines
Meanwhile, I'm the priest of this circus divine
the
the feet the grit is alive the mind is bleeding
steel screen black mirror eyes you talk divine while the signal dies born in static
in the towel storm in his head tarot on fire the spirits are fed father of madness the cat daddy
in the chat
I was like a country vibe, right a little bit. Yeah, I play a lot with like
Like fusing different styles. Yeah, you know shoes like from up to like 50 or 60 styles
And so they are really more and it should have like death metal and shit like heavy metal country rock like everything you say
right they can fuse it together with like like I'm like no we're Japanese styles and they all kinds of like
Just pop on man. Everyone's being Japanese
If you want to just hang and be chill come on man. Oh
Well, that was
um yeah i guess not video let's see there's some good ones um yeah is there one you have
we haven't heard at all maybe we'll see
spooky ghost over
So you want my fire, no I don't crave it, but I'll light it, step into my store, no I won't fight it, I'll ignite it, keep it strange divine, no morning, afternoon, fine, this feels like a glitch for me, we don't hear, we just create.
Be the kind of soul you can only touch in the astral
Yeah, we don't ride waves, we become the tidal
Call it devotion, maybe we should drop
Yeah, some of the lyrics in these songs are out of control.
But, I can't, I honestly cannot even get a little bit of lyrics.
It's all mean to the music and the graphic.
I think A.I. is gonna run like musicians out of the fucking bullpuck, bro
Maybe labels
I think everything it's just gonna be i music
Musicians are going to be whoever's producing the best A.I. team, I guess
Correct like who can compete with this shit? I rather listen to this shit than have the shit out like
I don't know. Yeah
You gonna pay to listen to someone when the people isn't helping better?
See this video is perfect with the song. Sometimes the AI hits it, like the song and the video match perfectly, sometimes it fucks up, like Paige having a beer.
Paige having a beer, that's cool.
That was nice.
Yeah, you know what I mean, that was perfect.
Yeah.
I dug that.
but you in the body storm has some weird shit like the guy eating the hot dog in my mind
like the grants or house whatever kind of deep
but this is kind of
a home that's okay yeah let me see
um
another one we haven't heard I don't think I've ever heard of
K-Lo's made of smoke, every tear you fake, chips, mercury, slow
Your mask is slipping through the cold, the hunger of the hollow
This ain't this wild old sorrow
service show me me heaven and hell we're binary lies when I ascend your ego dies
scar can you feel my power click here and your world gets smaller scar scar can you
feel my power one spark and your truth gets
Even in hell where empty dries, when I'm cold, no flesh survives
SCAR!
Can you feel my power?
Click here and your world gets smaller
SCAR SCAR!
Can you feel my power?
One spark and your truth gets darker
Cause I went to God just to see
And the mirror was watching me
Heaven and hell were both my screens
When I'm light, the dark reading
mother-lover
Now it said
Songs that I like but they're changed around you know and then put into like different styles
And so you don't recognize them, but some of them are based on
Um, but you know just like kind of change
Before I logged in
When I'm near you
Time falls like bad code
Meanin' deletes itself. I forget my own user name
report
again and again upload the story start it's very technical upload have a
chance of firewall for me
there's a song I'm locked in
firewall for me
that's so cool it's like tying the future
But that's the way our super futuristic being would think, have it as a part of opening.
The clock said 10 o'clock
That music like that was freaking me out man like what couldn't figure out what it's in it's just it's like
It was doing that scale climb like the bass that
And it wasn't quite matching with with the other thing i'm like what
This is freaking me out, man. I was totally cool
And I think I did that the other night, um, okay. Yeah, um
How many songs should have you made probably over 50
50 and we've probably seen what like 20 to 30 of them. Maybe yeah
I'm seeing all 50
Cause in the night we don't do
Just what
This is top five if not top three
And that's the difference right there
Not a piece of that baby
Not everyone's not a piece of that
Is it what Jamie's saying in chat
J-Hope, that voice sounds like someone or something. Yeah, someone.
Sike, he's not going to leave who I found.
Just like a playlist and just hit play off. Just let's just I know I can only do one
I don't think just play one after the other. Oh, yeah, I should actually yeah
Yes, but like an autoplay tool fucking
Yeah
Oh, so it's coming up actually oh really
Well perfect time I guess
Okay, later goats